<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Michu 39 Graham 90 9 January 2013 Last updated at 22:15 GMT Swansea won at Chelsea for the first time in 87 years to head into the Capital One Cup semi-final second leg with a precious two-goal advantage. The hosts dominated in the first half but an error from defender Branislav Ivanovic allowed Michu to curl home. The home side continued to press but Ivanovic was again at fault in stoppage time when Danny Graham seized on his poor backpass to seal the win. "If you look at Bradford and Swansea they both had a plan and were highly disciplined. Swansea really deserve to come away from this game with something. Michael Laudrup has communicated his plan, got his players focused and Michu stands out in sacrificing his creativity to do a job and they all worked very hard together. Chelsea are relying too much on the individual players rather than a collective plan but I would have expected them to have scored a couple of goals from the chances they had." Demba Ba thought he had snatched a late goal only for it to be ruled offside. The win puts Swansea firmly in command heading into the second leg at the Liberty Stadium on 23 January as they look to end a 100-year wait for a first major trophy. Chelsea, though, were the architects of their own downfall. They enjoyed plenty of possession throughout the encounter but were let down by poor decision-making in the final third. The home side spent the initial exchanges patiently passing the ball around as they probed for potential openings in the Swansea backline. They were nearly rewarded in the 11th minute when Oscar and Eden Hazard combined to unlock the Swansea defence and present Ramires with a chance on goal, but the midfielder's toe-poked effort lacked power and was comfortably saved by keeper Gerhard Tremmel. That early chance was not a sign of things to come, however, as play once again settled into a pedestrian pace, although Chelsea continued to dominate. Please turn on JavaScript. Media requires JavaScript to play.'Fantastic' Swansea delight Laudrup The home side did not trouble Tremmel again until the 26th minute when Hazard surged into the Swansea area before squaring a pass for the unmarked Juan Mata, but the Spaniard's low shot was gratefully scooped up by Tremmel. By now Chelsea were looking a confident side and Mata almost made amends for failing to make the most of that opportunity minutes later when he raced onto Oscar's smart back-heel but his shot trickled agonisingly wide of the far post. It seemed only a matter of time before Chelsea would take the lead but poor defending instead saw Swansea snatch the opener six minutes before the break. Ivanovic dithered with the ball just outside his own area and Jonathan de Guzman took full advantage, stealing possession before immediately passing to Michu and the in-form striker's curled effort flew beyond Ross Turnbull, taking his total for the season to 16. Michu was clearly a player brimming with confidence and he attempted an audacious overhead kick early in the second half, but the ball sailed harmlessly over Turnbull's goal. Please turn on JavaScript. Media requires JavaScript to play.Ba goal not offside - Benitez Tremmel maintained his side's slender advantage just before the hour when Hazard rolled the ball across the edge of the area for Luiz but his well-struck effort was kept out by the Swansea keeper. The visitors were clearly content to try and protect their lead, much to the frustration of the home side, who continued to try and carve out an opening. Frank Lampard replaced Ramires with 20 minutes remaining, before Ba was introduced 10 minutes later, replacing Fernando Torres as Chelsea interim manager Rafael Benitez looked to reinvigorate his attack. Ba quickly made his presence known and felt he should have had a penalty as the game entered stoppage time after clashing with Tremmel when challenging for possession, but instead he was booked for diving. Any hopes of Chelsea snatching an equaliser were ended shortly after as Ivanovic's poor backpass allowed substitute Graham to run in, round the keeper and fire into the empty net. Chelsea thought they had snatched what would have been a potentially important late goal when Ba powered a shot into the net from Lampard's knock on, but the striker had strayed just offside. Full Time The game is over, as the referee blows his whistle. Demba Ba is caught offside. Gerhard Tremmel takes the indirect free kick. Goal - Danny Graham - Chelsea 0 - 2 Swansea Danny Graham fires in a goal from inside the penalty area low into the middle of the goal. Chelsea 0-2 Swansea. Gerhard Tremmel takes the direct free kick. Booking Demba Ba booked for unsporting behaviour. Foul by Demba Ba on Gerhard Tremmel, free kick awarded. Shot from outside the penalty box by Cesar Azpilicueta goes wide right of the goal. Eden Hazard sends in a cross, clearance made by Pablo Hernandez. The ball is swung over by Ashley Cole, clearance made by Ben Davies. Centre by Marko Marin, Headed effort from deep inside the area by Demba Ba misses to the left of the goal. Branislav Ivanovic fouled by Angel Rangel, the ref awards a free kick. Branislav Ivanovic takes the direct free kick. The ball is crossed by Branislav Ivanovic, Demba Ba takes a shot. Save by Gerhard Tremmel. Juan Mata fouled by Dwight Tiendalli, the ref awards a free kick. Juan Mata takes the direct free kick. Shot on goal by David Luiz from long range goes harmlessly over the target. Danny Graham gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on Ashley Cole. Direct free kick taken by Ashley Cole. Substitution Danny Graham on for Miguel Michu. Substitution Emboaba Oscar goes off and Marko Marin comes on. Drilled right-footed shot by Frank Lampard. Gerhard Tremmel makes a comfortable save. Angel Rangel is flagged offside by the assistant referee. Gary Cahill takes the free kick. Substitution Demba Ba is brought on as a substitute for Fernando Torres. Eden Hazard crosses the ball. A cross is delivered by Cesar Azpilicueta, clearance made by Ashley Williams. Miguel Michu is caught offside. Indirect free kick taken by Ross Turnbull. Emboaba Oscar delivers the ball, save by Gerhard Tremmel. Foul by Sung-Yeung Ki on Eden Hazard, free kick awarded. Juan Mata restarts play with the free kick. Eden Hazard gives away a free kick for an unfair challenge on Chico. The ball is delivered by Jonathan de Guzman, Shot by Ashley Williams. Comfortable save by Ross Turnbull. Unfair challenge on Miguel Michu by Branislav Ivanovic results in a free kick. Free kick crossed right-footed by Jonathan de Guzman, David Luiz makes a clearance. Substitution Frank Lampard on for Nascimento Ramires. The ball is swung over by David Luiz, clearance made by Ashley Williams. Emboaba Oscar crosses the ball, Pablo Hernandez gets a block in. Eden Hazard fouled by Ben Davies, the ref awards a free kick. The free kick is delivered left-footed by Juan Mata from right channel. Nascimento Ramires has a mishit shot. Blocked by Sung-Yeung Ki. Inswinging corner taken from the right by-line by Juan Mata, clearance by Chico. Cesar Azpilicueta produces a cross, blocked by Ben Davies. Miguel Michu is caught offside. Free kick taken by Gary Cahill. Foul by Miguel Michu on Nascimento Ramires, free kick awarded. David Luiz takes the direct free kick. Unfair challenge on Sung-Yeung Ki by Nascimento Ramires results in a free kick. Direct free kick taken by Sung-Yeung Ki. Substitution Wayne Routledge goes off and Dwight Tiendalli comes on. Corner taken right-footed by Juan Mata, save by Gerhard Tremmel. Cesar Azpilicueta crosses the ball, blocked by Ben Davies. Shot by David Luiz. Save made by Gerhard Tremmel. Centre by Fernando Torres, comfortable save by Gerhard Tremmel. The ball is delivered by Fernando Torres, Chico manages to make a clearance. Unfair challenge on David Luiz by Jonathan de Guzman results in a free kick. Strike comes in from David Luiz from the free kick. The ball is delivered by Wayne Routledge, Effort on goal by Miguel Michu from inside the area goes harmlessly over the bar. Shot from just outside the area by Eden Hazard misses to the left of the target. Cesar Azpilicueta produces a cross, Gerhard Tremmel makes a comfortable save. Ashley Cole sends in a cross. Miguel Michu is caught offside. Gary Cahill takes the indirect free kick. Shot comes in from David Luiz from the free kick. Booking Chico goes into the book for unsporting behaviour. Chico challenges Fernando Torres unfairly and gives away a free kick. Eden Hazard fouled by Angel Rangel, the ref awards a free kick. David Luiz takes the direct free kick. The official flags Fernando Torres offside. Chico takes the free kick. The second half kicks off. Half Time The match has reached half-time. The ball is delivered by David Luiz, clearance made by Angel Rangel. Foul by Jonathan de Guzman on Branislav Ivanovic, free kick awarded. Juan Mata crosses the ball in from the free kick. Sung-Yeung Ki challenges Nascimento Ramires unfairly and gives away a free kick. Gary Cahill takes the free kick. Cesar Azpilicueta produces a right-footed shot from just outside the box that goes wide right of the target. Inswinging corner taken left-footed by Juan Mata from the right by-line to the near post, Fernando Torres produces a header from deep inside the six-yard box which goes wide of the right-hand post. Curled right-footed shot by Branislav Ivanovic. Save made by Gerhard Tremmel. Direct free kick taken by Juan Mata. Booking The referee shows Pablo Hernandez a yellow card for unsporting behaviour. Emboaba Oscar fouled by Pablo Hernandez, the ref awards a free kick. The assist for the goal came from Jonathan de Guzman. Goal - Miguel Michu - Chelsea 0 - 1 Swansea Miguel Michu finds the back of the net with a goal from the edge of the penalty box to the top left corner of the goal. Chelsea 0-1 Swansea. Effort from outside the box by David Luiz goes wide right of the target. Emboaba Oscar crosses the ball, clearance by Ashley Williams. The offside flag is raised against Miguel Michu. Gary Cahill takes the free kick. Fernando Torres delivers the ball, Gerhard Tremmel makes a comfortable save. Leon Britton fouled by Nascimento Ramires, the ref awards a free kick. Leon Britton takes the free kick. Shot by Juan Mata from deep inside the penalty area misses wide to the left of the target. Juan Mata has an effort at goal from 12 yards. Save made by Gerhard Tremmel. Outswinging corner taken from the right by-line by Emboaba Oscar, Header from deep inside the area by Gary Cahill goes over the bar. The ball is sent over by Juan Mata, clearance by Ben Davies. Long range shot by Gary Cahill goes wide right of the goal. Cesar Azpilicueta has an effort at goal from outside the area which misses left. Juan Mata takes a shot. Blocked by Ben Davies. Miguel Michu takes a shot. Save made by Ross Turnbull. Wayne Routledge delivers the ball, David Luiz manages to make a clearance. Cesar Azpilicueta concedes a free kick for a foul on Ben Davies. Direct free kick taken by Leon Britton. Fernando Torres is ruled offside. Ashley Williams takes the indirect free kick. A cross is delivered by Wayne Routledge, save made by Ross Turnbull. Juan Mata delivers the ball, clearance by Angel Rangel. Cesar Azpilicueta produces a cross, Ashley Williams manages to make a clearance. The referee blows for offside. Ashley Cole takes the indirect free kick. Nascimento Ramires takes a shot. Comfortable save by Gerhard Tremmel. Fernando Torres produces a right-footed shot from just outside the box that misses to the right of the net. Inswinging corner taken by Eden Hazard from the left by-line, Fernando Torres takes a shot. Centre by Ashley Cole, blocked by Chico. Fernando Torres crosses the ball, Branislav Ivanovic produces a header from inside the area that goes over the bar. Corner taken left-footed by Juan Mata. Emboaba Oscar delivers the ball, clearance by Ashley Williams. Jonathan de Guzman fouled by Nascimento Ramires, the ref awards a free kick. Pablo Hernandez takes the direct free kick. Sung-Yeung Ki challenges Emboaba Oscar unfairly and gives away a free kick. Direct free kick taken by Juan Mata. David Luiz challenges Leon Britton unfairly and gives away a free kick. Chico takes the direct free kick. The ref blows the whistle to start the match. Live text and data provided by The Press AssociationSign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. All posts are reactively-moderated
 and must obey the house rules The pent up rage & jealousy coming from the comments of people whose team are not involved in this competition is amazing. From Man U, Arsenal, Liverpool fans etc, this cup is pointless. If it's that pointless, wipe it from your honours list. As for these idiots who say that Swansea should be kicked out of the PL, they're more entertaining than the dross of Stoke/Sunderland/Wigan/QPR. Report this comment (Comment number 228) Link to this (Comment number 228) Quality from Swansea.

A full house at Stamford bridge and they said it was a Mickey Mouse cup. Rafa (as per) was to late with his substitution but that wasn't why they lost. Individual performances were shocking from ivanovic, mata and hazard and others. No service for Torres again. Report this comment (Comment number 227) Link to this (Comment number 227) This comment was removed because the moderators found it broke the house rules. Explain. Report this comment (Comment number 226) Link to this (Comment number 226) Well done Swansea, I know it is only half the job done but a half well done. They are a great example of a team that work for each other and have a great team spirit and make the best of what they have. As opposed to the prima donnas at the top clubs that have no respect for any part of the game, other players, the ref, the fans and each other. Report this comment (Comment number 225) Link to this (Comment number 225) I went to a Lge Cup Final a few years back. THFC v CFC. CFC fans had a banner in their end "CFC creating History 3X Lge Cup Winners". They lost. Their end was empty 5 minutes after the whistle. Didn't even clap their players.
Now its a "Mickey Mouse Cup".
Says it all, really, don't it. Report this comment (Comment number 224) Link to this (Comment number 224) Comments 5 of 228Add your commentSign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20886408</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 17:56 GMT Rangers will consider leaving Scottish football if plans to restructure the leagues are pushed through. Clubs are set to vote on a proposal which would create three divisions, with 12 teams in both of the top two leagues and 18 in the third flight. But Rangers chief executive Charles Green is not in favour of the plan. "If that's what we have sat here eagerly awaiting, my advice is the quicker we can leave Scottish football the better," he told the club website. " We might as well have a winter break from now until August. I can't see any point in carrying on with meaningless matches" Earlier this week, representatives of seven Scottish Premier League clubs and eight Scottish Football League clubs met with administrators from the governing bodies at Hampden. It was announced that teams will be asked to vote on the implementation of a Premier League of 12 sides, a Championship also of 12 and a National League of 18. However, Green, whose Rangers side are 17 points clear at the top of the Third Division, believes this plan would not make the league more appealing. He said: "I can't see anything that is going to transform the finances, the status or the excitement. "If this does happen, what is the point of us finishing the season? "Why should we send players out to get broken noses - like Ross Perry last week - or have players getting surgery when no-one can get promoted and no-one can get relegated? "We might as well have a winter break from now until August. I can't see any point in carrying on with meaningless matches. "In what league do you win a division and then end up playing the same teams again the following season? There is no meaning to it, in reality." The subject of Rangers and Celtic leaving Scotland has long been discussed but Green knows there is no existing escape route. Any club playing matches in Scotland needs the blessing of the Scottish Football Association, Uefa are currently opposed to cross-border leagues and England's top-flight has rejected the notion of welcoming the Old Firm. "On first glance, of course, there is nowhere for us to go because Fifa have made their feelings known on cross-border leagues," added Green. "Hand on heart, there isn't an option but that doesn't mean we shouldn't start looking for an option. "If all we have to look forward to over the next four years is more madness then we would be failing as directors not to explore the alternatives." However, Celtic chief executive Peter Lawwell insisted his side were "committed" to the SPL, and that the club supported the proposed reforms. "We support the SPL, we're committed to the SPL," he said. "We as a club support it. It's not perfect, but it's the best available, and I don't think you throw out the best in pursuit of the perfect. "I think it will be beneficial to the game." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20963963</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 23:04 GMT Blackburn Rovers have approached Blackpool for permission to speak to Tangerines boss Michael Appleton about the managerial vacancy at Ewood Park. Rovers sacked Henning Berg on 27 December but have won their last three games under caretaker Gary Bowyer. Appleton, 37, only joined Blackpool from Portsmouth in November as a replacement for Ian Holloway. Rovers managing director Derek Shaw said : "He is the only candidate we have approached." Appleton has only won two games since taking charge at Bloomfield Road, drawing eight and losing two, and has won just 15 games since making his managerial debut for Pompey in November 2011. Blackpool's last win came against Blackburn on 15 December and the two sides are one place apart in the Championship table. Rovers are in 13th place, five points short of the play-off places and one point above Blackpool. A short Blackpool statement confirmed that Rovers had made an approach for their manager. Last week, Rovers global advisor Shebby Singh told BBC Radio Lancashire that the club wanted their next manager to accept a short-term contract. Singh said: "If somebody has got the ambition, the knowledge and the experience, there will be people who will take the job. "We are looking to offer a short-term contract with specific targets, and upon achieving those targets it will trigger a longer-term contract." Sign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. All posts are reactively-moderated
 and must obey the house rules This comment is awaiting moderation. Explain. Report this comment (Comment number 70) Link to this (Comment number 70) Not had long enough at Blackpool to say how good he is,Gary Bowyer has a better record God help you. Report this comment (Comment number 69) Link to this (Comment number 69) When I read this, I thought it might be a joke.

Then I remembered Venky;'s own Blackburn. So it's most likely going to be another successful appointment!


Feel VERY sorry for you Blackburn fans at having to endure what Venkys are doing to you - if ONLY you spent more money on Chicken products round your way, maybe they'd lay off your club a bit. Report this comment (Comment number 68) Link to this (Comment number 68) Appleton is a great move by Blackburn. Forget about his abysmal record. Its unimportant. He has lost every dressing room on day one...so what? He loves chicken and that is what counts. As manager he must force the players to eat more chicken. that is the way out of trouble. Report this comment (Comment number 67) Link to this (Comment number 67) Im not convinced by Appleton the manager yet. He did 'OK considering' at Pompey and just 'OK' so far at Blackpool. Im even less convinced by the regime at Blackburn however,they clearly do not understand the club,it's history,it's supporters or the game itself and if I were Appleton or frankly anybody else I wouldn't touch the job with a bargepole. Report this comment (Comment number 66) Link to this (Comment number 66) Comments 5 of 70Add your commentSign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20967683</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 20:44 GMT Former Chelsea assistant manager Ray Wilkins says Manchester United would be a perfect destination for Frank Lampard if he leaves Stamford Bridge. The 34-year-old's deal expires in the summer and there is no sign of a contract extension. Wilkins, who played for Chelsea and United, says the midfielder would win more medals if he moved to the Reds. "He'll want to continue to win and play at a high level, and there's no higher level than Old Trafford," said Wilkins. Premier League title: 2004-05, 2005-06,2009-10 FA Cup: 2006-07, 2008-09, 2009-10, 2011-12 League Cup: 2004-05, 2006-07 Champions League: 2011-12 Lampard, who has won three Premier League titles and a Champions League with Chelsea, says he thinks he has "a good few more years" left at the top level. Wilkins maintains that United manager Sir Alex Ferguson is the ideal manager to get the best from Lampard, given his handling of 39-year-old Ryan Giggs and Paul Scholes, 38. "You have the master of utilising the older player in Sir Alex Ferguson so I think it would be a tremendous move for Frank and a good one for Manchester United as well," Wilkins told BBC Radio Manchester. "He's getting older but the knowledge of how to play the experience he's gained over the years will always stand him in good stead. "You only have to see the performances Giggs and Scholes themselves have put in over the last few years, and they are four years older than Frank." Former England international Wilkins does not think that Lampard would have any problems winning over the United fans after 10 years with one of their main rivals. "He'll win them over because of his footballing ability. If you look at Old Trafford, if anything they lack goals from the middle of the pitch," he added. Meanwhile, Juventus midfielder Andrea Pirlo says he would relish the chance to play alongside Lampard. "They would be mad to let him leave Chelsea. He's still one of the best in the world," said the 33-year-old Italy international. "If he wants to play in Italy I would welcome him to Juventus with open arms. Lampard could have another four years at the top in Italy." Chelsea fans chanted "sign him up" when Lampard came on as a substitute in the 5-1 FA Cup win at Southampton on Saturday. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20930630</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 23:46 GMT Swansea City manager Michael Laudrup praised his players' "fantastic fight" after their 2-0 Capital One Cup semi-final, first leg win at Chelsea. Goals by Michu and Danny Graham put the Swans in control for the second leg in Swansea on 23 January. "It was a fantastic fight," said Laudrup. "We knew it was going to be difficult... I cannot dream about a result like this." However, the Dane warned "there's a long way to go, believe me." Chelsea dominated possession and territory but were undone by two mistakes by Branislav Ivanovic. Please turn on JavaScript. Media requires JavaScript to play.'Fantastic' Swansea delight Laudrup The Serb was caught in possession for Michu's first-half opener - the Spaniard's 16th goal of the season - and his backpass in second-half injury time was pounced on by Graham for Swansea's second goal. Chelsea substitute Demba Ba had a goal disallowed after Graham's strike. Laudrup praised his team's ability to make the most of their chances as they moved closer towards a first major cup final appearance in their history. "The two goals were two mistakes by Chelsea, but again my players Michu and then Danny were there to take advantage," he said. "If you look at Bradford and Swansea they both had a plan and were highly disciplined. Swansea really deserve to come away from this game with something. Michael Laudrup has communicated his plan, got his players focused and Michu stands out in sacrificing his creativity to do a job and they all worked very hard together. Chelsea are relying too much on the individual players rather than a collective plan but I would have expected them to have scored a couple of goals from the chances they had." "If you take away the goals I still think part of all the possession they had they only created a few chances. "I counted only three big chances - Ramirez and Mata in the first half and the shot from Luis from close distance in the second half, apart from the disallowed goal which was an offside. "That's really not that much when you think that we played the at the ground of the European champions." The former Danish international said he was also happy with the way his team adapted their playing style in the face of Chelsea's domination. "You have to be realistic. You can't think that you can come here to play the European champions and have the ball 60% of the time like we have in the majority of our games," said Laudrup. "We knew we would have to do something extra - more without the ball than with the ball. "I think we showed that we have so much apart from quality as well as a lot of confidence in our team. "I'm so pleased that in two weeks' time we can come back and play at our ground with a possibility of going to that final." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/wales/20965177</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Lionel Messi has sent a signed shirt and personal message to Gerd Muller to recognise his previous status as record holder for scoring the most goals in a calendar year.

The Argentina captain - who was recently awarded the Ballon d'Or for the fourth year in succession - racked up 91 goals in 2012, six more than the total achieved by Muller for club and country in 1972.
 Don't Miss Pedro: Messi is the best player everRosell hails Messi's Ballon d'Or successMessi: I will reflect when I retireIniesta: Messi will win a fifth Ballon d'Or
Having broken new ground with his tally, Messi acted quickly in sending a Barcelona home shirt to the former Germany international with the player's name and number emblazoned on the back.

"For Gerd Muller, my respect and admiration, and a hug," the Argentine wrote on the shirt.

Club president Sandro Rosell also sent Bayern counterpart Karl-Heinz Rummenigge a letter expressing his recognition of Muller and the previous milestone, noting the record "was clearly an added motivation and target for Messi." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/12/spain/2013/01/10/3661137/messi-sends-muller-signed-shirt-after-breaki</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Massimiliano Allegri was satisfied with his players despite seeing his AC Milan team knocked out of the Coppa Italia quarter-finals by Juventus.
 Don't Miss Allegri: Juve are the strongest in ItalyBerlusconi: Results to decide Allegri fateAllegri: Robinho is focused on MilanAllegri unhappy with 'poor' Milan start
The Rossoneri seized the early initiative when Italy striker Stephan El Shaarawy put the away side ahead, but the game was turned on its head following Sebastian Giovinco's equaliser and Mirko Vucinic's extra-time winner.

The former Cagliari coach felt his side's performance was undermined by a self-inflicted error for the Bianconeri's winning goal, coupled with goalkeeping heroics, as they pressed for the goal that would have taken the game to penalties.

"It was a balanced game and on the second goal we made a mistake in defence that allowed the counterattack," Allegri told RAI.

"In any case, I am happy with the performance because we had several chances to equalise after Vucinic 's goal.

"It 's a shame about the result, especially with Marco Storari 's final save. We can improve, but we deserved more from this match." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/10/italy/2013/01/10/3661098/ac-milan-deserved-more-insists-allegri</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson is hopeful that the race row surrounding Patrice Evra and Luis Suarez is now firmly in the past as the Red Devils welcome Liverpool to Old Trafford on Sunday. Don't Miss Smalling 'relieved' to return to actionInce warns son Tom over Liverpool moveVidic: It will be tough to replace Sir AlexVan Nistelrooy offers backing for ButtnerWebb appointed ref for Man Utd v L'pool Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Man Utd. pound; 19.10 Draw pound; 37.50 Liverpool pound; 37.50 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Man Utd. pound; 18.33 Draw pound; 36.00 Liverpool pound; 43.33 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Man Utd. pound; 18.30 Draw pound; 37.50 Liverpool pound; 42.00 Suarez received a pound40,000 fine and eight-match ban for racially abusing Evra during a match in October 2011, while the Uruguayan star snubbed a proposed handshake when the two sides met four months later in February 2012. However, the two players have since played against each other and did exchange pleasantries earlier this season at Anfield, giving Sir Alex reason to be optimistic that it will not be an issue again on Sunday. Ferguson told reporters: "There will always be a certain build-up to a Manchester United and Liverpool games. "That's simply because of the history between the two clubs, the two most successful in the country - it brings its own agenda in terms of profile and pre-match discussion. "Last year it was unfortunate with the Suarez behaviour. But I think hopefully it's behind both clubs now and we can just look forward to the game." The 71-year-old also spoke about a rollercoaster 2012, a year fraught with disappointments from a United perspective - particularly the final day of the season when the Red Devils lost the title to neighbours Manchester City on goal difference. He continued: "There were a lot of ups and downs [in 2012]. It was disappointing. Firstly in European football we were knocked out the previous December and so we had to do without that. "We were knocked out in the second game of the FA Cup - very unluckily - at Liverpool. We should have won that game. That left us with the league and then we lost that on the last day of the season on goal difference. So it was very, very frustrating. "Since then we've done what we said we'd do. We qualified from the group stage of the Champions League. I thought we were unlucky to be knocked out of the League Cup by Chelsea, with the last kick of the ball, after we'd played so well. "The league so far has gone well and we're in a good position. We just now need to make sure we kick on, keep our concentration and keep playing our football the way we are." Despite strolling through their Champions League group and finishing in top spot with ease, United were awarded with arguably the toughest draw possible in the first knockout round against Real Madrid However, Ferguson believes they will have a great chance of winning the competition if they can get past Jose Mourinho's Spanish champions. He continued: "No doubt about that at all. You needn't fear anyone if you win that. I look at the competition this year and there are four teams we have to pay attention to. "Obviously we're drawn against one of them. If we get by that, then the likes of Borussia Dortmund, Bayern Munich and Barcelona will be there - Dortmund have been fantastic." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/9/england/2013/01/10/3661101/sir-alex-ferguson-hopes-evra-suarez-race-ro</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Cristiano Ronaldo has pleaded for Real Madrid supporters to stick together following the latest expression of dissent shown towards Jose Mourinho from the Santiago Bernabeu faithful.
 Don't Miss Match Report: Real Madrid 4-0 Celta VigoLeonardo hints at Ronaldo moveRonaldo is happy at Madrid, says AlonsoReal Madrid name strong Copa squad Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Man Utd. pound; 12.50 Draw pound; 50.00 West Ham United pound; 80.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Man Utd. pound; 13.00 Draw pound; 55.00 West Ham United pound; 90.00 
The coach's name was heckled when it was announced prior to Blancos' 4-0, Copa del Rey victory over Celta Vigo, with fans particularly unhappy with Iker Casillas' recent exclusion from the side and their poor Liga form.

While Mourinho was absent at the post-match press conference, Ronaldo - who struck a hat-trick in a superb individual display - called on fans to aid the team's pursuit of trophies by displaying their support in a positive manner.

"We must stand united and we need the fans to support us, there is still a lot to win," he told reporters.

The Portugal international's man-of-the-match display was saluted by Sergio Ramos after the game, though the evening ended on a more sour note for the defender after he was sent off.

"Ronaldo is very motivated, and I can see he is happy," the Spain defender said.

 "He deserves his standing ovation and that affection. He's the best in the world." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/12/spain/2013/01/09/3661034/ronaldo-we-need-real-madrid-fans-to-support-</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Rafa Benitez refused to criticise Fernando Torres after another uninspired performance saw him booed off by the Stamford Bridge crowd during Chelsea's shock 2-0 defeat to Swansea in the Capital One Cup.
 Don't Miss Match Report: Chelsea 0-2 SwanseaPlayer Ratings: Chelsea 0-2 SwanseaChelsea fans turn on Torres Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Everton pound; 15.30 Draw pound; 37.50 Swansea City pound; 60.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Everton pound; 15.71 Draw pound; 40.00 Swansea City pound; 55.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Everton pound; 15.70 Draw pound; 40.00 Swansea City pound; 60.00 
The pound50 million man was withdrawn in favour of Demba Ba on 81 minutes to a less than complimentary reception from the stands as his side trailed to a clinical Michu finish on the stroke of half-time.

It was the first sign that Blues fans have run out of patience with Torres, but Benitez insists his countryman should not be singled out for the defeat, and is adamant he is pleased with his side's performance.

When it was put to him that Ba accomplished more in nine minutes than the man he replaced had mustered in 81, the Chelsea boss countered: "I think we had chances at the end, but as a team we were creating chances from the first minute. It 's not just one player or the striker.

"You have Mata, Ramires, David Luiz - 23 attempts, so if you are playing against a team who is deep and you still have a lot of attempts. I 'm happy with the way the team was working. I don 't think we can talk about one player.

"We had a lot of chances, and could have scored two or three in the first half, one or two in the second half. We made two mistakes and paid for them. This is the reality.

"The team was attacking, playing possession and controlling against a good team who were defending."

The atmosphere of anger around Stamford Bridge turned positively poisonous as Danny Graham added a second for the visitors late on, but Benitez insists his team were not distracted by events off the pitch.

"You analyse all these things because we lost, but the way we played, the control we had, the chances we created, is what we have to do," he added. 

"We have to be more clinical in front of goal, but we were doing a lot of things really well."

The Spaniard also defended Branislav Ivanovic, whose two horrendous errors directly led to both goals, and praised the Serb's courage.

"Any player making mistakes is not a big issue," he continued. "The main thing is they try to do things after, and Ivanovic was trying to do his best, and the team was creating chances. 

"It's something that can happen in football, and the main thing is to keep going for the next game."

Swansea's victory - their first at Stamford Bridge since 1925 - leaves Chelsea's Capital One Cup hopes all but shattered, but Benitez remains adamant one goal at the Liberty Stadium could reverse his side's fortunes.

"They have a great advantage, but we have to go there and score a goal, and then we will be in the game," he concluded. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/9/england/2013/01/09/3661013/benitez-brushes-off-torres-criticism-after-</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Staying put ... Laudrup believes Michu will stay at Swansea City. Source: Alastair Grant / AP Michael Laudrup insists Michu will stay with Swansea during the January transfer after the Spanish striker put his side in sight of a place in the English League Cup final. Swansea manager Laudrup described the forward as the "bargain of the season'' following a 2-0 win away over European champions Chelsea in the first leg of their semi-final tie - the Welsh club's first victory at Stamford Bridge since 1925. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Michu, signed for STG2 million ($A3 million) from La Liga side Rayo Vallecano, scored his 16th goal in 25 appearances this season to give Swansea a 39th-minute lead in west London.His goal tally has made Michu a coveted target but Laudrup believes the 26-year-old's recent form had put him out of reach of all but Europe's wealthiest clubs."We all know the situation, the economic situation in the world, so there really aren't that many clubs who can buy him,'' Denmark great Laudrup said."There are some here in England. In Spain, there are only two. Italy, I don't think so,'' he added. "They're trying to sell. Bayern Munich in Germany ... so only a few, few clubs.Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar. Premier League Ladder P W D L GD Pts 1 Man United 21 17 1 3 26 52 2 Man City 21 13 6 2 22 45 3 Tottenham 21 12 3 6 12 39 4 Chelsea 20 11 5 4 20 38 5 Everton 21 9 9 3 9 36 6 Arsenal 20 9 7 4 18 34 7 West Brom 21 10 3 8 2 33 8 Liverpool 21 8 7 6 8 31 9 Swansea 21 7 8 6 5 29 10 Stoke 21 6 11 4 1 29 11 West Ham 20 7 5 8 0 26 12 Norwich 21 6 7 8 -10 25 13 Fulham 21 6 6 9 -5 24 14 Sunderland 21 5 7 9 -8 22 15 Newcastle 21 5 5 11 -12 20 16 Aston Villa 21 4 7 10 -24 19 17 Southampton 20 4 6 10 -11 18 18 Wigan 21 5 3 13 -17 18 19 Reading 21 2 7 12 -17 13 20 QPR 21 2 7 12 -19 13 Round 21 - as at 00:00 AM, 04/01/13 Round 21 - as at 00:00 AM, 04/01/13"And Michu likes it here. He's happy where he is, so I'm really not afraid because I'm so sure he will stay with us for the next five or six months. I don't know in the summer."I don't know how much he's worth - ask my chairman. He was the bargain of the season - we know that. But we're happy we've found the right players.''Turning to Michu's tally, Laudrup said: "What he is doing, in terms of goals, is incredible particularly when you think he's never been a number nine (striker).Read all the transfer whispers surrounding Swansea City star Michu"He's always been a midfielder coming from deeper. But one chance, one goal today. That's incredible. You'd pay a lot of money for that.''Victory moved Swansea, who face Chelsea in the return leg at their Liberty Stadium home on January 23, closer to a first major cup final appearance. Rumour Mill Gossip Here's the best gossip, speculation and fun as European managers dabble in the market. &lt;/p&gt; Here's the best gossip, speculation and fun as European managers dabble in the market.But Laudrup refused to accept his side were favourites to go through and play fourth-tier Bradford or Premier League rivals Aston Villa."We have a realistic possibility, but there's still a mountain to climb,'' he said with an unlikely final against Bradford looming after the Bantams' 3-1 first leg win over Villa on Tuesday.Mistakes from Chelsea defender Branislav Ivanovic allowed Michu and Danny Graham to clinch victory and inflict a second successive home defeat on Chelsea.But Rafael Benitez insisted there were plenty of positives to draw from the performance, despite being jeered once again by Blues' supporters."I think the team were doing really well, had a lot of chances and could have scored two or three in the first half, but made two mistakes and paid for them. That is the reality,'' interim manager Benitez said.]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/swansea-city-manager-michael-laudrup-confident-star-striker-mic</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Raring to go ... Michael Beauchamp returns from suspension for the Wanderers this week. Source: Marianna Massey / AAP As some teams begin to reach levels of desperation, here are the full squad lists for round 16 of the Hyundai A-League. A-League Round 16 Friday, January 11 Adelaide Adelaide vs Perth 7:30 PM Hindmarsh Stadium Perth Saturday, January 12 Victory Victory vs Central Coast 5:30 PM Aurora Stadium Central Coast Newcastle Newcastle vs Brisbane 7:45 PM Hunter Stadium Brisbane Sunday, January 13 Wellington Wellington vs Western Sydney 2:30 PM Westpac Stadium Western Sydney Sydney Sydney vs Heart 5:00 PM Allianz Stadium Heart All times are listed in EDT Adelaide United v Perth Glory, Hindmarsh Stadium, Friday 7.30pm (EDT), Fox Sports 1 HD 

Adelaide United squad: 1.Eugene Galekovic (gk) (c), 2.Osama Malik, 4.Jon McKain, 5.Iain Fyfe, 6.Cassio, 7.Zenon Caravella, 10.Dario Vidosic, 11.Bruce Djite, 12.Antony Golec, 14.Cameron Watson, 16.Daniel Bowles, 17.Iain Ramsay, 18.Fabian Barbiero, 20.Paul Izzo (gk), 21.Jeronimo Neumann, 23.Evan Kostopoulos, 24.Awer Mabil
*two to be omitted

In: Osama Malik (promoted), Jon McKain (promoted), Awer Mabil (promoted from NYL)

Out: Marcelo Carrusca (groin - 2-3 weeks)

Unavailable: Nigel Boogaard (hamstring - 1 week), Fabio Ferreira (groin - 2-3 weeks)

Perth Glory Squad: 1.Danny Vukovic (gk), 3.Bas van den Brink, 5.Steve Pantelidis, 6.Nick Ward, 7.Jacob Burns (c), 8.Dean Heffernan 9.Shane Smeltz, 10.Liam Miller, 11.Adrian Zahra, 12.Ryo Nagai, 13.Travis Dodd, 14.Steven McGarry, 15.Brandon O 'Neill, 17.Chris Harold, 18.Jesse Makarounas, 19.Josh Risdon, 21.Scott Jamison, 22.Ndumba Makeche, 30 Lewis Italiano (gk)
*four to be omitted

Ins: 3.Bas van den Brink (returns from suspension), 11.Adrian Zahra, 18.Jesse Makarounas, 22.Ndumba Makeche (all promoted)

Outs: Nil

Unavailable: 16.Evan Berger (hamstring - indefinite), 23.Michael Thwaite (calf - 2 weeks)Referee: Peter Green Who Made The Cut? The best: Simon Hill's A-League top 30: 6-1 + 31 Melbourne Victory v Central Coast Mariners, Aurora Stadium, Saturday 5:30pm (EDT), Fox Sports 1HD 

Melbourne Victory squad: 1. Tando Velaphi (GK), 2. Matthew Foschini, 3. Adama Traore, 5. Mark Milligan, 6. Leigh Broxham, 8. Jonathan Bru, 9. Marcos Flores, 10. Archie Thompson, 11. Marco Rojas, 14. Billy Celeski, 16. Theo Markelis, 17. Jimmy Jeggo, 21. Spase Dilevski, 23. Adrian Leijer, 24.Nick Ansell, 25. Luke O 'Dea, 26. Andrew Nabbout, 39. Nathan Coe (GK)
*three to be omitted

In: 2. Matthew Foschini, 16. Theo Markelis, 17. Jimmy Jeggo (all promoted)

Out: Nil

Unavailable: 7. Gui Finkler (knee)

Central Coast Mariners squad: 1. Mathew Ryan (Gk), 2. Daniel McBreen, 3. Joshua Rose, 4. Pedj Bojic, 5. Zachary Anderson, 6. Patrick Zwaanswijk, 7. John Hutchinson (c), 9. Bernie Ibini, 11. Oliver Bozanic, 13. Brent Griffiths, 14. Michael McGlinchey, 17. Anthony Caceres, 18. Nick Montgomery, 20. Justin Pasfield (Gk), 21. Mile Sterjovski, 23. Adam Kwasnik
*one to be omitted 

In: 6. Patrick Zwaanswijk (returns from injury) 

Out: 16. Trent Sainsbury (suspended - 1 week) 

Unavailable: 10. Tomas Rogic (suspended - 1 week), 22. James Oates (ankle - 2 months)Referee: Jarred GillettStart of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar. 2012-2013 A-League Season Schedule: Full A-League fixtures + 19 Fixtures: Heart-Victory starts new season + 48 Draw: All A-League finals to be 'knockout' + 62 Newcastle Jets v Brisbane Roar, Hunter Stadium, Saturday 7:45pm (EDT), Fox Sports 1 HD

Newcastle Jets squad: 1. Ben Kennedy 2. Scott Neville, 7. James Brown 8. Ruben Zadkovich, 9. Emile Heskey, 11. Connor Chapman, 12. Josh Brillante, 13. Sam Gallaway 14. Taylor Regan 15. Craig Goodwin, 16. Jobe Wheelhouse 17. James Virgili, 18. Jacob Pepper, 19. Michael Bridges 20. Mark Birighitti, 22. Adam Taggart, 23. Ryan Griffiths, 25. Mitch Cooper
*three to be omitted

In: Jobe Wheelhouse (returns from injury), Scott Neville, Mitch Cooper (promoted)

Out: Nil

Unavailable: Josh Mitchell (knee), Ben Kantarovski (knee), Dominik Ritter (hamstring)

Brisbane Roar squad: 1. Michael Theo (gk), 2. Matt Smith (c), 3. Shane Stefanutto, 4. Matt Jurman, 5. Ivan Franjic, 6. Erik Paartalu, 7. Besart Berisha, 8. Massimo Murdocca, 11. Ben Halloran, 15. James Donachie, 17. Mitch Nichols, 18. Luke Brattan, 20. Matt Acton (gk), 21. James Meyer, 22. Thomas Broich, 24. Nick Fitzgerald, 25. George Lambadaridis
*two to be omitted

In: James Donachie (returns from suspension), Luke Brattan (promoted)

Out: Nil

Unavailable: Jack Hingert (hip injury - 4-6 weeks), Do Dong-Hyun (knee - 2-3 weeks), Henrique (hip injury - 1-2 weeks)

Referee: Strebre Delovski A-League App Stay across all the action no matter where you are! Also available from the Android Market - get it now! Wellington Phoenix v Western Sydney Wanderers FC, Westpac Stadium, Sunday 2:30pm (EDT), Fox Sports 1HD

Wellington Phoenix squad: 1. Mark Paston (GK), 3. Tony Lochhead, 6. Alex Smith, 7. Leo Bertos, 9. Benjamin Totori, 10. Stein Huysegems, 11. Jeremy Brockie, 12. Tyler Boyd, 15. Cameron Lindsay, 16. Louis Fenton, 17. Vince Lia, 18. Ben Sigmund, 21. Dani Sanchez, 22. Andrew Durante (C), 30. Griffin McMaster (GK)

In: 12. Tyler Boyd (returns from suspension)

Out: Michael Boxall (omitted) 

Unavailable: 8. Paul Ifill (ankle injury 3-4 weeks), Manny Muscat (suspended - 1 week)

Western Sydney Wanderers FC squad: 1. Ante Covic (GK), 2. Shannon Cole, 3. Adam D 'Apuzo, 4. Nikolai Topor-Stanley, 5. Michael Beauchamp, 6. Jerome Polenz, 7. Labinot Haliti, 8. Mateo Poljak, 10. Aaron Mooy 11. Tarek Elrich, 13. Joey Gibbs, 14. Kwabena Appiah-Kubi, 15. Reece Caira, 17. Youssouf Hersi, 18. Iacopo La Rocca, 19. Mark Bridge, 20. Jerrad Tyson (GK), 21. Shinji Ono
*three to be omitted

In: Youssouf Hersi (returns from suspension), Michael Beauchamp (returns from suspension), Adam D 'Apuzzo (promoted), Mateo Poljak (Promoted)

Out: 23. Jason Trifiro (suspended - 1 match)

Unavailable: Tahj Minniecon (foot - indefinite), Dino Kresinger (knee 2-3 weeks)

Referee: Shaun Evans 

 A-League Ladder P W D L GD Pts 1 Central Coast 15 10 3 2 15 33 2 Adelaide 15 9 2 4 7 29 3 Victory 15 8 2 5 0 26 4 Western Sydney 15 7 2 6 4 23 5 Perth 15 5 4 6 2 19 6 Heart 15 5 3 7 -2 18 7 Brisbane 15 5 2 8 0 17 8 Newcastle 15 5 2 8 -9 17 9 Wellington 15 4 4 7 -3 16 10 Sydney 15 4 2 9 -14 14 Round 15 - as at 00:00 AM, 06/01/13 Round 15 - as at 00:00 AM, 06/01/13Sydney FC v Melbourne Heart, Allianz Stadium, Sunday 5pm (EDT), Fox Sports 1 HD 

Sydney FC squad: 2. Sebastian Ryall, 3. Fabio, 6. Jason Culina, 7. Brett Emerton, 10. Alessandro Del Piero, 12. Blake Powell, 15. Terry McFlynn, 16. Joel Chianese, 17. Terry Antonis, 18. Trent McClenahan, 20. Vedran Janjetovic (gk), 21. Yairo Yau, 22. Ali Abbas, 23. Rhyan Grant, 26. Peter Triantis, 28. Aaron Calver, 33. Matthew Nash (gk)
*two to be omitted

In: Fabio (returns from injury), Yairo Yau (returns from injury)

Out: Nil

Unavailable: Pascal Bosschaart (calf - 2 weeks), Ivan Necevski (ankle - 2 weeks ),Nathan Sherlock (hamstring - 2 weeks)

Melbourne Heart FC Squad: 1.Clint Bolton (Gk), 3. Cameron Edwards, 4.Simon Colosimo, 5.Fred (c), 6. Patrick Gerhardt, 8. Matthew Thompson, 9.Dylan Macallister, 10. Josip Tadic, 11. Richard Garcia, 13. Jonatan Germano,14. Golgol Mebrahtu, 16. Aziz Behich, 17. Jason Hoffman,18. David Vrankovic, 19. Ben Garuccio, 20. Andrew Redmayne (GK), 21. Steven Gray, 22. Nick Kalmar, 24. Sam Mitchinson, 25. Jeremy Walker, 26. Ersin Kaya
*six to be omitted

Ins: 3. Cameron Edwards, 18. David Vrankovic, 19. Ben Garuccio, 21. Steven Gray, 22. Nick Kalmar, 24. Sam Mitchinson, 25. Jeremy Walker, 26. Ersin Kaya (all promoted)

Outs: 2.Michael Marrone (impending transfer), 15. David Williams (suspended - one match)

Unavailable: 23.Mate Dugandzic (broken foot - season) 31. Vince Grella (groin - undisclosed)

Referee: Peter O'Leary
]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/a-league/all-the-squads-ahead-of-round-16-of-the-2012-2013-a-le</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Friday Five ... what's on Adam's list this week? Source: Fox Sports Each week this football season, Fox Sports football commentator Adam Peacock selects five reasons for tuning in to the Barclays Premier League and A-League. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.THE TROUBLE WITH LUIS SUAREZWhy is it never boring with Luis Suarez? Never one to illicit a carefree reaction amongst football watchers, he is either a victim of his own greatness, or the most unlikable of the unloved. The reaction to his handball goal in the FA Cup was predictable, but it raged nonetheless. Religious leaders got involved, everyone had their say. It was in truth, a goal the referee alone has to overrule. It all happened so quick, it couldn 't have been premeditated.But it had to be Suarez. A victim and perpetrator all in one, every time.Is it fair to feel sorry for him? Liverpool fans do and will, and as mentioned countless times before, fair enough. They love the shirt, and what 's inside it. For the rest? They don 't, and never will, because accidents or otherwise keep happening, and it 's very hard for a guy without a command of the lingo to defend himself through the press. So he doesn 't even try. That 's not to say I feel sorry for him. Just seems it doesn 't bother him, so why should anyone else worry about his feelings? EPL Guide 2012 Season Guide The offical guide to 2012-2013 Barclays Premier League season. Essential reading for fans. &lt;/p&gt; 2012-13 Barclays Premier League season guide! The offical guide to 2012-2013 Barclays Premier League season. Essential reading for fans.Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.He entered the country with a target on his back, signing for Liverpool while suspended for biting. And the reputation was there before his unusual dinner in Holland: the general theme after he stopped Ghana winning a World Cup quarter final with his hand? Well, not good - this from the Guardian live commentary of the game: "Grudging respect to the cheating little sods. It takes a real streak of evil to win like this".So then, it was always going to be a battle for the general football fan in England and Barclays Premier League watchers (Liverpool aside) to like Luis Suarez. You get the sense he 's quite OK with it, and what else would follow last weekend but Manchester United at Old Trafford this Sunday. Perhaps his idea of the perfect weekend. An intriguing character, one that helps the world go round. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.HOW DO YOU END AN ERA?Unlike Suarez, one man who it seems doesn 't mind his football career being played out in the press is Frank Lampard. He 's leaving Chelsea, he 's not, he 's playing out the season, Manchester United want him, QPR want him, Arsenal want him, Tom Cruise wants him in LA.He 's trying to win a PR battle, forcing Chelsea to have no option but to keep him. Or his advisors hope. Ahhhmm&hellip; does Roman Abramovich not care much for popularity contests? One day very soon, it will happen to John Terry. The club will want to move on. Terry might not. The saga with Lampard might just be an entree. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.ROBIN VAN PERFECTSome interesting stats did the rounds this week surrounding Robin van Persie and his worth to Manchester United, or interesting if you forget about reality. Without van Persie and his 16 goals and 6 assists, Manchester United would have only won 5 Premier League games and be on 26 points with West Ham in 11th. All very good to make that assertion - except for the fact Sir Alex Ferguson needed a striker and if he didn 't get van Persie, would he have got the top scorer for the Cumbria Plumbers XI?Sure, van Persie is phenomenal, and without him, the top of the table might look a little different. Certainly not a 7 point gap to Manchester City. But a quality player would have been purchased and now scoring goals. Not at the rate of the Dutchman (73 in his last 100 PL games!), but still, contributing. And Manchester United wouldn 't be 11th. All hypothetical anyway - less imaginary, the thought van Persie will have a huge bearing on this Sunday 's Manchester United-Liverpool battle. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.SWANNING ALONGThere was an afterlife for Swansea when Brendon Rodgers left after last season 's impressive Premier League debut. And it 's even better. Wembley and perhaps League Cup glory beckons. Michael Laudrup is getting a heap of praise. The parts he brought with him - like Michu - have improved what was there, and the 15 million pounds received for Joe Allen looks a good bit of a business all of a sudden. Yet the Dane is not getting carried away. Just enjoying the moment. For he 's had a few big moments in football before, as he so beautifully pointed out to the Mirror newspaper this week...Question: "You played with Pep Guardiola at Barcelona..."Michael Laudrup leans forward in his chair in the small manager 's office at the Liberty Stadium and interrupts."He would maybe say that he played with me."1-0. Premier League Fixtures and Results When and where is your team playing in the Barclays Premier League this season? &lt;/p&gt; EPL fixtures and results When and where is your team playing in the Barclays Premier League this season?PREMIER XIThe Premier League has Michael Laudrup, but La Liga has the best players, apparently. Players from around the world voted, and, in case you missed it, the FIFA/FIFPro X1 was - Iker Casillas, Dani Alves, Gerard Pique, Sergio Ramos, Marcelo, Xavi, Xabi Alonso, Andres Iniesta, Cristiano Ronaldo, Radamel Falcao, Lionel Messi.Five Real Madrid, five Barcelona, one Atletico Madrid. So the Premier League misses out, much to the mirth of those who think it 's an overhyped, fast food version of football. Much to the annoyance of those who think no other league exists. Much to the mild surprise of many, including yours truly. Rumour Mill Gossip Here's the best gossip, speculation and fun as European managers dabble in the market. &lt;/p&gt; Here's the best gossip, speculation and fun as European managers dabble in the market.If I had the chance to pick a team from the Premier League to try and beat the Latino Kings, here goes -Joe Hart; 
Pablo Zabaleta; Vincent Kompany; Nemanja Vidic; Leighton Baines
Lucas; Yaya Toure; Juan Mata 
Luis Suarez; Robin van Persie; Gareth BaleLucas?!?! Whhhaaat? They keep the ball OK, I suppose, and he 's good at getting the thing back. Steven Gerrard said so ;)Argue away&hellip;]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/premier-league/fox-sports-adam-peacocks-five-things-to-keep-an-</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Teen debut ... Mabil will get his first start with United against Perth. Source: Sarah Reed / News Limited Adelaide United have punted on a Kenyan teenager to fill a void in what coach John Kosmina terms a dangerous time of the A-League season. A-League Squads Round 16 We present all the squads for round 16 of the 2012-2013 Hyundai A-League season. &lt;/p&gt; Ins, outs: A-League squads: round 16 We present all the squads for round 16 of the 2012-2013 Hyundai A-League season.Awer Mabil, a 17-year-old who came to Australia in 2006, has been summoned for Friday night's encounter against Perth Glory as injuries begin to mount on the second-placed Reds.Mabil will come from the bench in his A-League debut at Hindmarsh Stadium to help cover the losses of Portuguese winger Fabio Ferreira and Argentine attacker Marcelo Carrusca, both sidelined by groin injuries."Awer has earned his chance from his performances in the youth team and he gives us a lot of speed and an x-factor," Kosmina told reporters on Thursday. A-League Preview Mel's Tips Fox Sports' Mel McLaughlin previews the coming round of the Hyundai A-League. &lt;/p&gt; Analysis: Mel's A-League preview: R16 Fox Sports' Mel McLaughlin previews the coming round of the Hyundai A-League."The youth team is there for occasions like this where you have got a number of different injuries. If you look at him and Fabio, it's almost like for like. They're both quick - they're both natural right wide players."Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.Adelaide hold second spot, four points shy of league leaders Central Coast and three points ahead of third-placed Melbourne Victory.Kosmina said along with some injuries, the Reds also had three players carrying four yellow cards - five yellows is punished with an automatic one-match ban. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player."It is going to get harder," Kosmina said. "The other teams have got better and we have still played in patches and played well. It is a dangerous time."You do get your niggles, and we have got three players on four yellows as well, so there will be a turnaround of starting line-up in the next month, I would imagine."Kosmina, who refused to talk about his coaching contract expiring at season's end, was wary of Perth and their striker Shane Smeltz, who scored twice in a 2-2 draw with Sydney FC last start."They are tough mentally and they are tough physically," Kosmina said of the Glory."We have got to be aware of Smeltzy ... he has learnt to think his way through the game, which he wasn't doing when he was a lot younger."So he's smart, he makes good runs, he gets into good areas at the right time and he's an exceptional finisher."]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/a-league/adelaide-united-pick-17-year-old-awer-mabil-for-friday</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Big names, big dollars ... Edinson Cavani, Theo Walcott and Leighton Baines Source: FOX SPORTS It's looking like 50 Shades of Blue as Chelsea, Manchester City, and Everton get busy on the English transfer scene. Could Cavani find a home at Manchester City?City assistant coach Angelo Gregucci has admitted to Sky Sports that his club is, in fact, interested in the highly-regarded Napoli striker Edinson Cavani. The 25-year-old is arguably the most sought-after European forward, with 24 goals in 20 starts this season. City see the Uruguayan as the ideal recruit after missing out on Robin van Persie 's signature in 2012. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Are Chelsea about to sign the next big thing?

Brazillian gun Taison Freda is attracting admiring glances from Chelsea and Manchester City, with Rafa Benitez reportedly having the upper hand in signing the 20-year-old. The Guardian is reporting that his current club, Ukrainian side Metalist Kharkiv, wants between pound11m and pound13m from teams wanting to acquire the midfielder.Can Everton keep Leighton Baines?

Enjoying some excellent form this season after being reunited with left-side partner Steve Pienaar, the England international has been linked with Manchester United in recent days. The lack of European football with Everton may lead Baines to chase a club with that is a regular qualifier. United would fit the bill perfectly, wouldn 't you think.

Could the 'holy trinity ' at Chelsea gain a fourth arm?

The exhilarating trio of Juan Mata, Eden Hazard and Oscar could be further supported by highly-rated youngster Isco. The 20-year-old Spaniard, who currently plays for Malaga in Spain, certainly possesses skills worthy of the Chelsea 's attacking midfield. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.Is Becks heading to the Middle East?

The Sun is reporting that an unspecified club in Qatar has offered David Beckham a lucrative two-year contract. With the nation hosting the FIFA World Cup in 2022, Beckham 's move to Qatar would most certainly involve some sort of ambassadorial role for the tournament as well, drawing the big bucks for Becks.Will Zaha finally put pen to paper?

Seemingly linked at one point to every top-flight team in the EPL, it appears that England sensation Wilfried Zaha is about to sign with Manchester United. Zaha would most likely cost United around pound12-15m, which they would comfortably make up for with the sale of Nani.Have the Gunners kept their man?

Theo Walcott has reportedly been offered a pound25m contract to stay at Arsenal, and for that type of money, it 's likely he will stay put. The reported five-year contract would be worth about pound88,000 per week - not bad money for a 23-year-old. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Do Spurs have a new strike weapon?

The Telegraph is reporting that Tottenham Hotspur are close to signing striker Leandro Damiao for pound15m from Brazilian side Internacional. With Emmanuel Adebayor reportedly set for a departure after this season, the purchase of Damiao would be an ideal establishment of a rock-solid frontline in the future. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/premier-league/chelsea-manchester-city-and-everton-dominate-tod</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Home Y! Sports Experts Y! Sports Blogs Photo Galleries Rivals.com Video Y! Sports Radio Action Sports NFL NFL Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video NFL This Week Fantasy Football Fantasy 101 Fantasy Football Live Survival Football Outside the Game Blog Picks Tickets MLB MLB Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video Big League Stew Tickets Playoffs NBA NBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video NBA Highlights Video Coverage Featured Plays On Point Ball Don't Lie News Tickets NHL NHL Home Puck Daddy News Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video Photos Tickets NCAAF Home News Previews Recaps Scores & Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Boards Video Road To Saturday Blog Picks Odds Tickets NCAAB NCAAB Home News Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Board Odds Video Blog Tickets NASCAR NASCAR Home Schedule and Results Standings Stats Drivers Tracks Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Truck Series Nationwide Series Fantasy Photos From The Marbles Tickets News Head2Head Golf Golf Home Pro Tours Schedule Stats Players Leaderboard Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Nationwide Photos Devil Ball Golf Instruction Equipment Courses/Travel Tickets UFC MMA Home Rankings Schedule Video Photos Cagewriter Twitter Tickets UFC PPV: UFC 155 Boxing Boxing Home Rankings Results Schedule Champions Video Photos Blog Tickets Soccer More Rivals.com Rivals High Rivals High Home Prep Rally News Message Boards High School BCS Rivals High TV Olympics Home Schedule Fourth-Place Medal Photos Team Mom Beijing 2008 Vancouver 2010 MLS MLS Home Schedule Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets Tennis Tennis Home Rankings Matches Schedule Players Video Busted Racquet Photos Tickets NCAAW NCAAW Home Scores and Schedules Rankings Standings Stats Teams Photos News Previews Recaps WNBA WNBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Photos Cycling Cycling Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog IndyCar IndyCar Home Standings Schedule Video Photos CFL (CA) Horse Racing Horse Racing Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog Winter Sports Winter Sports Home Photos Skiing Schedule Results: Men Results: Women Standings: Men Standings: Women Investigations ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Fantasy GamesFootball Basketball Hockey Pro Pick'em Bowl Pick'em Golf Sports IQ World Soccer Home MLS Fixtures Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets England Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Spain Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Italy Fixtures and Results Weekly Report History Germany Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Netherlands Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History France Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Team USA Dirty Tackle Discover Yahoo! With Your Friends Loginclose FACTBOX-Soccer-African Nations Cup finalists MaliReuters - 5 hours ago Email 0 Recommend 0 Tweet 0 Jan 10 (Reuters) - Factbox on African Nations Cup finalists Mali ahead of this year's tournament in South Africa from Jan. 19 to Feb. 10: Previous appearances African Nations Cup finals: 7 Best performance: Runners-up: 1972; Third: 2012 FIFA world ranking Dec 2012: 25th Coach: Frenchman Patrice Carteron played briefly on loan at Sunderland in 2001, scoring from his defensive position in the derby against Newcastle United. The rest of his playing career was spent in France. He managed Cannes and led Dijon to promotion to Ligue 1 in 2011. Carteron lost his job just before the end of their debut season in the top flight as they went straight back down. Key players: Seydou Keita (Dalian Aerbin). Age: 32 (33 on Jan. 16). Pos: Midfielder Keita was a teenage prodigy at Olympique Marseille but failed to deliver on his early promise and spent time at Lorient and Racing Lens before moving to Spain in 2007. His transfer from Sevilla to Barcelona in May 2008 was valued at some 14-million euros and he played with the Catalans until last May, after which he left for China. Momo Sissoko (Paris St Germain). Age: 27. Pos: Midfielder Sissoko has not played for Mali since the 2010 Nations Cup, first shunning subsequent call-ups following a disappointing tournament in Angola and then once reconciled with the side missing out because of injury. Mali are taking a punt on his fitness by picking him for the 2013 finals. Modibo Maiga (West Ham United). Age: 25. Pos: Forward Played at the last two African Nations Cup finals but at the 2012 tournament in Equatorial Guinea and Gabon he missed the later stages after contracting malaria. Moved to London in July from Sochaux. Prospects: Mali have climbed to their highest position in the FIFA world rankings and have seemingly overcome the political turmoil after the coup in the country in March. They were surprise bronze medal winners at the 2012 finals and will expected to at least get through to the knockout stages again. (Compiled by Mark Gleeson in Cape Town; Editing By Alison Wildey) @yahoosports on Twitter, become a fan on Facebook Explore Related Content1 - 4 of 20prev next Soccer-Sissoko back in Mali squad for Nations &hellip;BAMAKO, Jan 3 (Reuters) - Hard-tackling Momo Sissoko is set to return to Mali's national team three years &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Sissoko back in Mali squad for Nations Cup Reuters Soccer-Niger name squad for African Nations &hellip;Jan 7 (Reuters) - Niger have retained 16 players from the last African Nations Cup in their squad of &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Niger name squad for African Nations Cup Reuters Soccer-Dembele gets first Mali call-up ahead &hellip;BAMAKO, Jan 8 (Reuters) - Mali have called up uncapped striker Mana Dembele from French club Clermont &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Dembele gets first Mali call-up ahead of Nations Cup Reuters Soccer-Diarra ruled out by injury but Sissoko &hellip;BAMAKO, Jan 9 (Reuters) - Injury has ruled out former captain Mahamadou Diarra from Mali's final squad &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Diarra ruled out by injury but Sissoko picked by Mali Reuters Katherine Webb didn&#x2019;t see any need for ESPN apology about Brent Musburger&#x2019;s commentsOregon&#x2019;s &#x2018;Rudy&#x2019; gets into Fiesta Bowl thanks to teammate faking an injuryMaloofs nearing deal to sell Kings to group that plans to relocate franchise to SeattleAJ McCarron, girlfriend Katherine Webb enjoying limelight after fixation sparks Internet fervorNo one will be admitted to the Hall of Fame from the writer&#x2019;s ballot this seasonTexas A&M OT Luke Joeckel declares for 2013 NFL draft, could be first overall pickMark Cuban was fined for tweeting about officials, raising new questionsRobert Griffin III has surgery to repair the LCL, ACL in right kneeNFL star's inspiring daily disease battleVote fails to sanitize the Hall of FameWhat Apple may have in store for 2013NRA's latest strategy to protect gunsTaco Cid's 'immigrant' shirts spark angerThe best single-serve coffee makers are ...Why Obama wants Lew for Treasury headDebit card thief's shipping blunder Yahoo! SportsHome NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy More Yahoo! Sports &#xBB; Also On Yahoo!Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert All Yahoo! &#xBB; Trending NowBody of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks Home NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert Body of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Click For Restrictions - http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Copyright &#xA9; 2013 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved. | Yahoo! - ABC News Network | Help / Suggestions Privacy Policy About Our Ads Terms of Service Copyright/IP Policy ]]></content>
 <link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/sports/rss/sow/SIG=136269rmn/*http%3A//sports.yahoo.com/news/factbox-soccer-a</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Home Y! Sports Experts Y! Sports Blogs Photo Galleries Rivals.com Video Y! Sports Radio Action Sports NFL NFL Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video NFL This Week Fantasy Football Fantasy 101 Fantasy Football Live Survival Football Outside the Game Blog Picks Tickets MLB MLB Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video Big League Stew Tickets Playoffs NBA NBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video NBA Highlights Video Coverage Featured Plays On Point Ball Don't Lie News Tickets NHL NHL Home Puck Daddy News Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video Photos Tickets NCAAF Home News Previews Recaps Scores & Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Boards Video Road To Saturday Blog Picks Odds Tickets NCAAB NCAAB Home News Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Board Odds Video Blog Tickets NASCAR NASCAR Home Schedule and Results Standings Stats Drivers Tracks Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Truck Series Nationwide Series Fantasy Photos From The Marbles Tickets News Head2Head Golf Golf Home Pro Tours Schedule Stats Players Leaderboard Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Nationwide Photos Devil Ball Golf Instruction Equipment Courses/Travel Tickets UFC MMA Home Rankings Schedule Video Photos Cagewriter Twitter Tickets UFC PPV: UFC 155 Boxing Boxing Home Rankings Results Schedule Champions Video Photos Blog Tickets Soccer More Rivals.com Rivals High Rivals High Home Prep Rally News Message Boards High School BCS Rivals High TV Olympics Home Schedule Fourth-Place Medal Photos Team Mom Beijing 2008 Vancouver 2010 MLS MLS Home Schedule Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets Tennis Tennis Home Rankings Matches Schedule Players Video Busted Racquet Photos Tickets NCAAW NCAAW Home Scores and Schedules Rankings Standings Stats Teams Photos News Previews Recaps WNBA WNBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Photos Cycling Cycling Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog IndyCar IndyCar Home Standings Schedule Video Photos CFL (CA) Horse Racing Horse Racing Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog Winter Sports Winter Sports Home Photos Skiing Schedule Results: Men Results: Women Standings: Men Standings: Women Investigations ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Fantasy GamesFootball Basketball Hockey Pro Pick'em Bowl Pick'em Golf Sports IQ World Soccer Home MLS Fixtures Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets England Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Spain Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Italy Fixtures and Results Weekly Report History Germany Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Netherlands Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History France Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Team USA Dirty Tackle Discover Yahoo! With Your Friends Loginclose FACTBOX-Soccer-African Nations Cup finalists NigerReuters - 5 hours ago Email 0 Recommend 0 Tweet 0 Jan 10 (Reuters) - Factbox on African Nations Cup finalists Niger ahead of this year's tournament in South Africa from Jan. 19 to Feb. 10: Previous appearances in African Nations Cup finals: 1 FIFA world ranking Dec 2012: 105 Coach: Gernot Rohr guided co-hosts Gabon to the quarter-finals of the last Nations Cup, where they were unlucky to lose on penalties. He took over the Niger job in September. The 59-year-old played at Bayern Munich and Girondins Bordeaux and then coached Bordeaux when they lost to Bayern in the 1996 UEFA Cup final. Key players: Moussa Maazou (Etoile Sahel) Age: 24. Pos: Forward Bulldozing forward whose has been the country's highest profile export to Europe, playing at Bordeaux, Monaco, Le Mans, CSKA Moscow and lastly in Belgium, but unable to pin down a long term contract. He has now moved to Tunisia in the hopes of restoring his club career. Daouda Kassaly (Chippa United). Age: 29 Pos: Goalkeeper Played for Cameroon club Coton Sport in the 2007 African Champions League final and won four league titles with the club. Before he was also a national champion in Niger with Sahel SC. He moved to the South African league in 2012 to join newly promoted Chippa United of Cape Town. Kamilou Daouda (JS Saoura). Age: 25 Pos: Forward Well-travelled striker who has played at clubs in Cameroon, Libya, Tunisia and, since July, with the newly promoted JS Saoura in the top flight of Algerian football. Had his best spell at Al Ittihad in Libya but was forced to flee when the league stopped there in March 2011 because of the rebellion against Muammar Gaddafi's regime. Prospects: Niger were evidently out of their depth at the 2012 finals in Equatorial Guinea and Gabon, where they made their Nations Cup debut but lost all three first round group games. They again had good fortune in the 2013 qualifiers and surprisingly return for a second successive tournament but without the prospect of bettering their performance of 12 months ago. (Compiled by Mark Gleeson in Cape Town; Editing by Tom Pilcher) @yahoosports on Twitter, become a fan on Facebook Explore Related Content1 - 4 of 20prev next Mideast Qatar Bayern Munich Schalke Socc &hellip; Soccer-Niger name squad for African Nations &hellip;Jan 7 (Reuters) - Niger have retained 16 players from the last African Nations Cup in their squad of &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Niger name squad for African Nations Cup Reuters Soccer-Advisory note on African Nations Cup &hellip;Jan 8 (Reuters) - Reuters will be moving an extensive African Nations Cup preview package over the next &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Advisory note on African Nations Cup package Reuters REFILE-Soccer-Ethiopia hold Tunisia to draw &hellip;(Changes Ethiopia's group from B to C in para 4) DOHA, Jan 7 (Reuters) - Ethiopia served notice of their &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;REFILE-Soccer-Ethiopia hold Tunisia to draw in warmup match Reuters Katherine Webb didn&#x2019;t see any need for ESPN apology about Brent Musburger&#x2019;s commentsOregon&#x2019;s &#x2018;Rudy&#x2019; gets into Fiesta Bowl thanks to teammate faking an injuryMaloofs nearing deal to sell Kings to group that plans to relocate franchise to SeattleAJ McCarron, girlfriend Katherine Webb enjoying limelight after fixation sparks Internet fervorNo one will be admitted to the Hall of Fame from the writer&#x2019;s ballot this seasonTexas A&M OT Luke Joeckel declares for 2013 NFL draft, could be first overall pickMark Cuban was fined for tweeting about officials, raising new questionsRobert Griffin III has surgery to repair the LCL, ACL in right kneeAl Gore's staggering personal fortuneHarrowing tale of Indian victim's journeyObama signals complete Afghan withdrawalA vodka cocktail that isn't lameThis is the NFL's likely No. 1 draft pickThe time Halle Berry was homelessHome-invasion shooting joins gun debateBest deal: Weight Watchers or Jenny Craig? Yahoo! SportsHome NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy More Yahoo! Sports &#xBB; Also On Yahoo!Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert All Yahoo! &#xBB; Trending NowBody of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks Home NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert Body of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Click For Restrictions - http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Copyright &#xA9; 2013 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved. | Yahoo! - ABC News Network | Help / Suggestions Privacy Policy About Our Ads Terms of Service Copyright/IP Policy ]]></content>
 <link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/sports/rss/sow/SIG=1370sqnhc/*http%3A//sports.yahoo.com/news/factbox-soccer-a</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Home Y! Sports Experts Y! Sports Blogs Photo Galleries Rivals.com Video Y! Sports Radio Action Sports NFL NFL Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video NFL This Week Fantasy Football Fantasy 101 Fantasy Football Live Survival Football Outside the Game Blog Picks Tickets MLB MLB Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video Big League Stew Tickets Playoffs NBA NBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video NBA Highlights Video Coverage Featured Plays On Point Ball Don't Lie News Tickets NHL NHL Home Puck Daddy News Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video Photos Tickets NCAAF Home News Previews Recaps Scores & Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Boards Video Road To Saturday Blog Picks Odds Tickets NCAAB NCAAB Home News Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Board Odds Video Blog Tickets NASCAR NASCAR Home Schedule and Results Standings Stats Drivers Tracks Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Truck Series Nationwide Series Fantasy Photos From The Marbles Tickets News Head2Head Golf Golf Home Pro Tours Schedule Stats Players Leaderboard Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Nationwide Photos Devil Ball Golf Instruction Equipment Courses/Travel Tickets UFC MMA Home Rankings Schedule Video Photos Cagewriter Twitter Tickets UFC PPV: UFC 155 Boxing Boxing Home Rankings Results Schedule Champions Video Photos Blog Tickets Soccer More Rivals.com Rivals High Rivals High Home Prep Rally News Message Boards High School BCS Rivals High TV Olympics Home Schedule Fourth-Place Medal Photos Team Mom Beijing 2008 Vancouver 2010 MLS MLS Home Schedule Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets Tennis Tennis Home Rankings Matches Schedule Players Video Busted Racquet Photos Tickets NCAAW NCAAW Home Scores and Schedules Rankings Standings Stats Teams Photos News Previews Recaps WNBA WNBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Photos Cycling Cycling Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog IndyCar IndyCar Home Standings Schedule Video Photos CFL (CA) Horse Racing Horse Racing Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog Winter Sports Winter Sports Home Photos Skiing Schedule Results: Men Results: Women Standings: Men Standings: Women Investigations ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Fantasy GamesFootball Basketball Hockey Pro Pick'em Bowl Pick'em Golf Sports IQ World Soccer Home MLS Fixtures Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets England Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Spain Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Italy Fixtures and Results Weekly Report History Germany Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Netherlands Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History France Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Team USA Dirty Tackle Discover Yahoo! With Your Friends Loginclose FACTBOX-Soccer-African Nations Cup finalists GhanaReuters - 5 hours ago Email 0 Recommend 0 Tweet 0 Jan 10 (Reuters) - Factbox on African Nations Cup finalists Ghana ahead of this year's tournament in South Africa from Jan. 19 to Feb. 10: Previous appearances in African Nations Cup finals: 18 Best performance: Winners: 1963, 1965, 1978, 1982; Runners-up: 1968, 1970, 1992, 2010 FIFA world ranking Dec. 2012: 30th Coach: Kwesi Appiah was promoted to the head coach after serving as the assistant to several of his predecessors. He was an international defender in his playing days with Asante Kotoko and then worked in the Ghana Football Association's coaching structure. He had a previous spell as coach after the 2010 World Cup but only on a caretaker basis for six months. Key players: Kwadwo Asamoah (Juventus). Age: 24. Pos: Midfielder Signed by Italian champions Juventus from Udinese in June, he was a teenage debutant for the Black Stars. Played at the 2010 World Cup in South Africa and is now close to 50 caps for the country. Operates effectively behind the strikers. Asamoah Gyan (Al-Ain). Age: 27. Pos: Forward A missed penalty with the final kick of the game cost Ghana a World Cup semi-final place in 2010. Gyan won widespread sympathy for his trauma but that turned to derision last year when his lack of form at the Nations Cup in Equatorial Guinea and Gabon contributed to Ghana's failure to reach the final. Christian Atsu (FC Porto). Age: 21 Pos: Winger The new hope of Ghana football who has emerged into the side since the last Nations Cup and who is expected to be among the young stars of the tournament. He was first brought into the Porto squad aged 17 by Andre Villas-Boas but this is his first season with regular game time. Prospects: Ghana will be among the favourites for the tournament, although they are without Andre and Jordan Ayew and have lost the influence of injury prone John Mensah in defence. The heavy burden of expectation on the team has sunk them repeatedly in the past and it is now more than 30 years since they won the last of their four Nations Cup titles. (Compiled by Mark Gleeson in Cape Town, Editing by Tom Pilcher) @yahoosports on Twitter, become a fan on Facebook Explore Related Content1 - 4 of 20prev next Soccer-Niger name squad for African Nations &hellip;Jan 7 (Reuters) - Niger have retained 16 players from the last African Nations Cup in their squad of &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Niger name squad for African Nations Cup Reuters Soccer-Advisory note on African Nations Cup &hellip;Jan 8 (Reuters) - Reuters will be moving an extensive African Nations Cup preview package over the next &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Advisory note on African Nations Cup package Reuters Soccer-Dede Ayew excluded from Ghana squad &hellip;Jan 7 (Reuters) - Winger Andre Ayew has been excluded from Ghana's squad for this month's African Nations &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Dede Ayew excluded from Ghana squad over fitness doubts Reuters Soccer-Bolasie replaced in DR Congo Nations &hellip;KINSHASA, Jan 1 (Reuters) - Yannick Bolasie has been replaced in the provisional Democratic Republic &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Bolasie replaced in DR Congo Nations Cup squad Reuters Katherine Webb didn&#x2019;t see any need for ESPN apology about Brent Musburger&#x2019;s commentsOregon&#x2019;s &#x2018;Rudy&#x2019; gets into Fiesta Bowl thanks to teammate faking an injuryMaloofs nearing deal to sell Kings to group that plans to relocate franchise to SeattleAJ McCarron, girlfriend Katherine Webb enjoying limelight after fixation sparks Internet fervorNo one will be admitted to the Hall of Fame from the writer&#x2019;s ballot this seasonTexas A&M OT Luke Joeckel declares for 2013 NFL draft, could be first overall pickMark Cuban was fined for tweeting about officials, raising new questionsRobert Griffin III has surgery to repair the LCL, ACL in right kneeRosie O'Donnell's surprise baby newsHapless NBA team may be changing citiesVote fails to sanitize the Hall of FameHome-invasion shooting joins gun debateDumb crook's alleged Olympics gaffePsy films new Super Bowl commercialRest in pieces: Monopoly token getting axedSix dangerous career myths to ignore Yahoo! SportsHome NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy More Yahoo! Sports &#xBB; Also On Yahoo!Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert All Yahoo! &#xBB; Trending NowBody of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks Home NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert Body of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Click For Restrictions - http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Copyright &#xA9; 2013 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved. | Yahoo! - ABC News Network | Help / Suggestions Privacy Policy About Our Ads Terms of Service Copyright/IP Policy ]]></content>
 <link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/sports/rss/sow/SIG=137128kdc/*http%3A//sports.yahoo.com/news/factbox-soccer-a</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Home Y! Sports Experts Y! Sports Blogs Photo Galleries Rivals.com Video Y! Sports Radio Action Sports NFL NFL Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video NFL This Week Fantasy Football Fantasy 101 Fantasy Football Live Survival Football Outside the Game Blog Picks Tickets MLB MLB Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video Big League Stew Tickets Playoffs NBA NBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video NBA Highlights Video Coverage Featured Plays On Point Ball Don't Lie News Tickets NHL NHL Home Puck Daddy News Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video Photos Tickets NCAAF Home News Previews Recaps Scores & Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Boards Video Road To Saturday Blog Picks Odds Tickets NCAAB NCAAB Home News Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Board Odds Video Blog Tickets NASCAR NASCAR Home Schedule and Results Standings Stats Drivers Tracks Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Truck Series Nationwide Series Fantasy Photos From The Marbles Tickets News Head2Head Golf Golf Home Pro Tours Schedule Stats Players Leaderboard Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Nationwide Photos Devil Ball Golf Instruction Equipment Courses/Travel Tickets UFC MMA Home Rankings Schedule Video Photos Cagewriter Twitter Tickets UFC PPV: UFC 155 Boxing Boxing Home Rankings Results Schedule Champions Video Photos Blog Tickets Soccer More Rivals.com Rivals High Rivals High Home Prep Rally News Message Boards High School BCS Rivals High TV Olympics Home Schedule Fourth-Place Medal Photos Team Mom Beijing 2008 Vancouver 2010 MLS MLS Home Schedule Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets Tennis Tennis Home Rankings Matches Schedule Players Video Busted Racquet Photos Tickets NCAAW NCAAW Home Scores and Schedules Rankings Standings Stats Teams Photos News Previews Recaps WNBA WNBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Photos Cycling Cycling Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog IndyCar IndyCar Home Standings Schedule Video Photos CFL (CA) Horse Racing Horse Racing Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog Winter Sports Winter Sports Home Photos Skiing Schedule Results: Men Results: Women Standings: Men Standings: Women Investigations ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Fantasy GamesFootball Basketball Hockey Pro Pick'em Bowl Pick'em Golf Sports IQ World Soccer Home MLS Fixtures Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets England Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Spain Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Italy Fixtures and Results Weekly Report History Germany Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Netherlands Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History France Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Team USA Dirty Tackle Discover Yahoo! With Your Friends Loginclose UPDATE 2-Soccer-Chelsea slump to shock home loss to Swansea in CupBy Tony Jimenez | Reuters - 5 hours ago Email 0 Recommend 0 Tweet 0 * Michu and Graham give Swansea 2-0 win * European champions Chelsea beaten in first leg (Adds detail) LONDON, Jan 9 (Reuters) - Swansea City inflicted the second shock home defeat in eight days on Chelsea, goals from Michu and Danny Graham giving the Welsh club a 2-0 win in their Capital One (League) Cup semi-final first leg on Wednesday. Michael Laudrup's Swansea, playing in their first major semi-final for 49 years, weathered an early storm from the European champions before scoring against the run of play in the 39th minute. Branislav Ivanovic blundered after receiving a pass from goalkeeper Ross Turnbull and Jonathan De Guzman robbed the Chelsea defender on the edge of the box before setting up Michu for a curling left-foot finish. It was the Spaniard's 16th goal of the season in all competitions and substitute Graham delivered a sucker-punch second goal near the end. "Winning an away game against the European champions is obviously very special," Laudrup told Sky Sports. "We knew it would be a very difficult game, we had to defend a lot more than we are used to. They had a lot more possession than we had." Chelsea, who also lost 1-0 at home to Premier League bottom club Queens Park Rangers last Wednesday, started well against Swansea but paid a heavy price for poor finishing. Juan Mata and Ramires shot weakly when well placed while Gary Cahill headed narrowly over from a corner. ACROBATIC SAVE Swansea then struck completely against the run of play through Michu before Ivanovic tried to make amends for his error when his rasping 20-metre shot was saved acrobatically by Gerhard Tremmel. The home fans became agitated in the second half as four-times League Cup winners Chelsea struggled to create clear-cut openings, calling for substitutes Frank Lampard and Demba Ba to come on. Lampard replaced Ramires in the 70th minute and new signing Ba went on for a completely ineffective Fernando Torres 11 minutes later. Swansea then delivered a second goal in stoppage time when substitute Graham latched on to a short Ivanovic back pass and rounded Turnbull before sliding the ball into an empty net. Ba, bought from Newcastle United last week, had the ball in the net in the closing stages but it was chalked off. "We had chances, the team had chances and we have to take our chances," Chelsea's interim manager Rafael Benitez said. "It's a Cup competition and we can score goals, if we score a goal everything will change," he added in reference to the second leg. Swansea captain Ashley Williams, named man of the match for a towering display in defence, said: "The second goal gives us little bit of a cushion but we know they are going to come at us with everything at our place. "I said to the guys before that this was the game of our lives. We are halfway there...and if we do get to the final at Wembley it will be massive for everyone." It was the second surprise result in successive days in the League Cup, fourth tier Bradford City having beaten Premier League Aston Villa 3-1 in their first leg on Tuesday. Both second legs are in two weeks' time. (Editing by Alison Wildey) @yahoosports on Twitter, become a fan on Facebook Explore Related Content1 - 4 of 20prev next Britain Soccer Soccer-Benitez rues misses after Swansea &hellip;LONDON, Jan 9 (Reuters) - Chelsea were booed off after losing 2-0 at home to Swansea City in a Capital &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Benitez rues misses after Swansea smash and grab win Reuters Britain Soccer League Cup Soccer-Swansea upset Chelsea in League C &hellip;LONDON, Jan 9 (Reuters) - Goals from Michu and Danny Graham gave Swansea City a 2-0 win at Chelsea in &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Swansea upset Chelsea in League Cup Reuters Katherine Webb didn&#x2019;t see any need for ESPN apology about Brent Musburger&#x2019;s commentsOregon&#x2019;s &#x2018;Rudy&#x2019; gets into Fiesta Bowl thanks to teammate faking an injuryMaloofs nearing deal to sell Kings to group that plans to relocate franchise to SeattleAJ McCarron, girlfriend Katherine Webb enjoying limelight after fixation sparks Internet fervorNo one will be admitted to the Hall of Fame from the writer&#x2019;s ballot this seasonTexas A&M OT Luke Joeckel declares for 2013 NFL draft, could be first overall pickMark Cuban was fined for tweeting about officials, raising new questionsRobert Griffin III has surgery to repair the LCL, ACL in right kneeThe indisputable reality of saving earlySource: Extensive damage to RG3's kneeVirginia resident calls 911 over 'baby lion'Popular drink linked to depressionThief leaves behind embarrassing trailCuban's few words earn him a huge fineBest deal: Weight Watchers or Jenny Craig?Obama signals complete Afghan withdrawal Yahoo! SportsHome NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy More Yahoo! Sports &#xBB; Also On Yahoo!Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert All Yahoo! &#xBB; Trending NowBody of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks Home NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert Body of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Click For Restrictions - http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Copyright &#xA9; 2013 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved. | Yahoo! - ABC News Network | Help / Suggestions Privacy Policy About Our Ads Terms of Service Copyright/IP Policy ]]></content>
 <link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/sports/rss/sow/SIG=133lmvaq4/*http%3A//sports.yahoo.com/news/2-soccer-chelsea</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Home Y! Sports Experts Y! Sports Blogs Photo Galleries Rivals.com Video Y! Sports Radio Action Sports NFL NFL Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video NFL This Week Fantasy Football Fantasy 101 Fantasy Football Live Survival Football Outside the Game Blog Picks Tickets MLB MLB Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video Big League Stew Tickets Playoffs NBA NBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video NBA Highlights Video Coverage Featured Plays On Point Ball Don't Lie News Tickets NHL NHL Home Puck Daddy News Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video Photos Tickets NCAAF Home News Previews Recaps Scores & Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Boards Video Road To Saturday Blog Picks Odds Tickets NCAAB NCAAB Home News Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Board Odds Video Blog Tickets NASCAR NASCAR Home Schedule and Results Standings Stats Drivers Tracks Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Truck Series Nationwide Series Fantasy Photos From The Marbles Tickets News Head2Head Golf Golf Home Pro Tours Schedule Stats Players Leaderboard Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Nationwide Photos Devil Ball Golf Instruction Equipment Courses/Travel Tickets UFC MMA Home Rankings Schedule Video Photos Cagewriter Twitter Tickets UFC PPV: UFC 155 Boxing Boxing Home Rankings Results Schedule Champions Video Photos Blog Tickets Soccer More Rivals.com Rivals High Rivals High Home Prep Rally News Message Boards High School BCS Rivals High TV Olympics Home Schedule Fourth-Place Medal Photos Team Mom Beijing 2008 Vancouver 2010 MLS MLS Home Schedule Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets Tennis Tennis Home Rankings Matches Schedule Players Video Busted Racquet Photos Tickets NCAAW NCAAW Home Scores and Schedules Rankings Standings Stats Teams Photos News Previews Recaps WNBA WNBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Photos Cycling Cycling Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog IndyCar IndyCar Home Standings Schedule Video Photos CFL (CA) Horse Racing Horse Racing Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog Winter Sports Winter Sports Home Photos Skiing Schedule Results: Men Results: Women Standings: Men Standings: Women Investigations ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Fantasy GamesFootball Basketball Hockey Pro Pick'em Bowl Pick'em Golf Sports IQ World Soccer Home MLS Fixtures Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets England Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Spain Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Italy Fixtures and Results Weekly Report History Germany Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Netherlands Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History France Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Team USA Dirty Tackle Discover Yahoo! With Your Friends Loginclose Soccer-Ecstatic Cape Verde ready to dance despite setbacksBy Miguel Pereira | Reuters - 6 hours ago Email 0 Recommend 0 Tweet 0 FARO, Portugal, Jan 10 (Reuters) - A series of player withdrawals has failed to dampen the party mood for Cape Verde who make their debut at the African Nations Cup (CAN) finals next week in South Africa. The archipelago nation in West Africa with a population of 500,000 is still ecstatic at becoming the smallest country to ever reach the finals thanks to a shock 3-2 aggregate win over four-times winners Cameroon in a playoff in October. But midfielder Odair Fortes and Braga forward Ze Luis pulled out of the squad this week to be replaced by striker Rambe and winger Platini from Portuguese clubs Belenenses and Santa Clara, respectively. "I don't think that the group is more fragile because of these absences," defender Fernando Varela told Reuters. Varela, of Romanian club Vaslui was not discounting further upsets from the "Tubaroes Azuis" (blue sharks), who kick off the tournament against hosts South Africa on Jan. 19 and will also face Morocco and Angola in Group A. "We know everybody is eyeing us because we knocked out Cameroon and we don't go there to mess around," he said as his team mates started practising at their training camp at the Algarve stadium in southern Portugal. "We want to win every match and do our best - expect rigor and hard work." Those are the values national coach Lucio Antunes, on leave from his job as an air traffic controller, must have had reinforced by Real Madrid's Jose Mourinho when he spent a week with the Portuguese learning some tricks of the trade last month. Antunes' first concern will be to patch up his 23-man squad already missing the key figures of defender Ricardo, captain Lito and striker Dady before the late withdrawals. However, these setbacks do not seem to have affected the squad's spirit. "We are newbies. But the nervousness is gone because nerves were just for the qualifying," Cape Verde's football director Heldeberto Ribeiro said. "Now that we are through, we must be tranquil and focus." The team will take the buoyant beats of "funana" music with them to South Africa. A funana-influenced song blasted from a speaker and captured the mood at the training camp. "The people are happy, Cape Verde is in the CAN. Oh yes we can," went the tailor-made tribute song by Cape Verde's duo Ay Tcla and Janett Lobo. (www.facebook.com/ay.tcla) The players sing, smile, bounce and clap at to the tune while they tie their boot laces in one of the dugouts. "As you can see the group is well. We feel like a family, like we are at home. Everyone wants to be here," Varela said. (Writing by Daniel Alvarenga; Editing by Alison Wildey) @yahoosports on Twitter, become a fan on Facebook Explore Related Content1 - 4 of 20prev next South Africa Soccer Soccer-Two late changes for Cape Verde's &hellip;Jan 9 (Reuters) - Midfielder Odair Fortes and striker Ze Luis have withdrawn from the Cape Verde Islands &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Two late changes for Cape Verde's Nations Cup squad Reuters Gale Agbossoumonde Soccer-Cape Verde hold Nigeria to drawJan 9 (Reuters) - Tiny Cape Verde Islands served notice of their potential at the upcoming African Nations &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Cape Verde hold Nigeria to draw Reuters Katherine Webb didn&#x2019;t see any need for ESPN apology about Brent Musburger&#x2019;s commentsOregon&#x2019;s &#x2018;Rudy&#x2019; gets into Fiesta Bowl thanks to teammate faking an injuryMaloofs nearing deal to sell Kings to group that plans to relocate franchise to SeattleAJ McCarron, girlfriend Katherine Webb enjoying limelight after fixation sparks Internet fervorNo one will be admitted to the Hall of Fame from the writer&#x2019;s ballot this seasonTexas A&M OT Luke Joeckel declares for 2013 NFL draft, could be first overall pickMark Cuban was fined for tweeting about officials, raising new questionsRobert Griffin III has surgery to repair the LCL, ACL in right kneeThief leaves behind embarrassing trailMeet Rod Stewart's rockin' broodWhy Saban shouldn't leave Alabama for NFLHilary Duff's amazingly bendable bodyWait, that's actually a Burger King?Kate Middleton's most infamous lookHome upgrades that are a waste of moneyHapless NBA team may be changing cities Yahoo! SportsHome NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy More Yahoo! Sports &#xBB; Also On Yahoo!Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert All Yahoo! &#xBB; Trending NowBody of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks Home NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert Body of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Click For Restrictions - http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Copyright &#xA9; 2013 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved. | Yahoo! - ABC News Network | Help / Suggestions Privacy Policy About Our Ads Terms of Service Copyright/IP Policy ]]></content>
 <link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/sports/rss/sow/SIG=13cb9r8ks/*http%3A//sports.yahoo.com/news/soccer-ecstatic-</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Please turn on JavaScript. Media requires JavaScript to play.Ba goal not offside - Benitez 9 January 2013 Last updated at 23:40 GMT Chelsea interim manager Rafael Benitez says the European champions paid the price for mistakes made in the Capital One Cup semi-final first-leg clash as Swansea won 2-0 at Stamford Bridge. Branislav Ivanovic was at fault for both goals, losing possession as Michu curled in the first before his backpass gifted Danny Graham the second. Chelsea had plenty of chances to score but were wasteful near goal. "We made two mistakes and paid for them," said Benitez. While the defensive errors proved costly, Chelsea had 24 attempts at goal, compared with Swansea's five, but only eight of those were on target. "We were doing a lot of good things but in football you have to take your chances," Benitez added. Chelsea have failed to score in four of Rafael Benitez's six home games in charge - but scored 14 in the other two "If we played this game 10 times, maybe we would win nine of them." Benitez was unhappy that substitute Demba Ba had a goal ruled out in stoppage time for offside and that the Senegal striker was booked for an apparent dive in the penalty area. "The goal was a goal - he was level," Benitez said. "The penalty and yellow card, it wasn't a yellow card. The penalty depends on the decision of the referee." Benitez refused to blame Serbian defender Ivanovic for the defeat. "I can see any player making mistakes. It's not a big issue," he said. "It's something that can happen, and the main thing is we have to carry on and try again. "Obviously they have a great advantage but we have to go there, try to score a goal and we will be in the game." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20967721</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 21:42 GMT Inverness Caledonian Thistle boss Terry Butcher has rejected an offer to become Barnsley manager. The 54-year-old was given permission to open talks with the Championship strugglers on Monday. However, the former England captain has elected to stay with the Highland side. "It was a very tough decision because Barnsley made me feel so welcome. They're extremely passionate for the club but we've started something at Inverness ," he told the BBC. " "We're obviously very disappointed. We put a lot of effort in trying to recruit Terry" "This is the best season of my managerial career - but it's only halfway through and I want to finish the season off in style and continue the good work we've started." Butcher took over at Inverness in January 2009 and has guided the club to second in the Scottish Premier League and they face Hearts in the League Cup semi-final this month. And the former England centre-half said that loyalty to the players and staff he has brought to Inverness meant he had to stay. "It's one of the hardest decisions I've ever had to make," added Butcher. "Under any other circumstances, I would have jumped at the chance. But for me it's something special that we've got here and I never really wanted to leave. "It's a good job for someone and perhaps in the future that could be me. " Inverness chairman Kenny Cameron also said he was relieved at Butcher's decision to remain with the club. "When Barnsley made their approach we felt that out of courtesy we should allow Terry the opportunity to meet with them," he said. "But it is a huge relief that he has opted to stay." The Tykes, who are bottom of the Championship, have been without a manager since sacking Keith Hill on 29 December. Barnsley director Don Rowing told BBC Radio Sheffield: "We're obviously very disappointed. We put a lot of effort in trying to recruit Terry. "I was sure we convinced him that Barnsley was the right club for him. "It's not finances that have determined his decision. I think it's purely the fact that he's taken stock of where he is with Inverness." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20963656</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 17:47 GMT Togo have selected Emmanuel Adebayor for the Africa Cup of Nations after the Tottenham striker reversed his decision not to play in the tournament. The 28-year-old Togo captain will join the squad after Tottenham's Premier League match against QPR on Saturday. Adebayor initially planned to remain with his club because of a row over team security and unpaid bonuses. But the striker will travel to South Africa after talks with the country's president Faure Gnassingbe. "It is to do something extraordinary and I know that the fans know what I am capable of doing," said Adebayor. His absence for the tournament, which starts on 19 January, will leave Tottenham with Jermain Defoe as their only recognised striker. After QPR, Tottenham host Manchester United on 20 January before travelling to Leeds or Birmingham in the fourth round of the FA Cup on 26 January. Away games against Norwich and West Brom precede the visit of Newcastle on 9 February, with the Cup of Nations ending the following day. Adebayor has scored only three goals in 17 appearances this season and in his absence, the goalscoring burden will rest largely with Defoe, who has struck 14 times in 28 games this term. Winger Gareth Bale is second in Tottenham's scoring charts on 11 goals, while forward Clint Dempsey has six and winger Aaron Lennon three. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20941373</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 21:34 GMT An Italian government watchdog (ONMS) has said public security officials will be given the power to stop football matches in cases of racist behaviour. A match could either be abandoned or temporarily stopped to warn supporters. The director of public order services will have the "sole responsibility" to suspend a match after talks between the referee and the fourth official. Last week AC Milan walked out of a friendly after midfielder Kevin-Prince Boateng was subjected to racist chants. Boateng, 25, has since said he would walk off the field again if subjected to racist abuse and Milan owner Silvio Berlusconi praised the player for his stand against racism. Fifa president Sepp Blatter described Boateng's stance as courageous, but did not believe such gestures would provide a long-term solution to the problem. ONMS, a department of the interior ministry, said the problem was caused by a small minority, while adding that violence at Italian matches was also on the decline. "There has been a further drop in the number of violent incidents, while manifestations of racism and intolerance sporadic and always limited to a restricted group," a statement read. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20963080</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 22:00 GMT Inter Milan have accepted a bid from Turkish club Galatasaray for Netherlands midfielder Wesley Sneijder. Galatasaray are believed to be prepared to pay 10 million euros (&#xA3;8.2m) for the 28-year-old and meet his wage demands. Inter president Massimo Moratti said: "Galatasaray's offer satisfies us. Now it depends on the player." Sneijder, who was strongly linked with Manchester United last summer, has not played for Inter since 25 September because of a dispute over his contract. It remains to be seen whether the playmaker will agree to move to Turkey, having suggested he would only consider one of Europe's top few teams. In November, the Italian side informed Sneijder he would not play for them until he agreed a significant cut in his salary. The player refused, meaning he has been on the sidelines despite being fit for the past two months. Sign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. All posts are reactively-moderated
 and must obey the house rules Unlikely he's willing to go to Turkey. Not before the the last hrs of the window at least. Only if there's no English top club for him by then the 6 mln euros on the Turkish table might get him to move to Istanbul. Question is, is he still interesting enough after 2 mediocre seasons. A manager would need to make him feel as important as Mourinho did at Inter. Hard to see that happening right now. Report this comment (Comment number 144) Link to this (Comment number 144) Inter are vindictive, small and unispiring team, who will never attract biggest name players. They also play unfair. Murinho left them. Snider siged a contract, which is he is righfully sticking to. Now they want to offload him at cut price because they want revenge. Do you think it would be right for him to demand more if he was a Balon D'or winner? Report this comment (Comment number 143) Link to this (Comment number 143) Another thing as well.If he's thinking about money.In UK he has to pay 50% in tax.In Turkey the max he will have to pay is 35% so on 200k a week he would only get roughly 100k in UK and 130k a week in Turkey. That's &#xA3;1.5m extra a year in Turkey. For the money it would make sense to go to Turkey.He pays 43-46% in Italy now. Depends what he wants more, good money or top class football at his prime. Report this comment (Comment number 142) Link to this (Comment number 142) 8.2 million. 200k a week means in a year he will have cost them 18 million and 28 million in 2 years. If Galatasaray think one of the best midfielders in the world in his peak years is worth 28-33 million overall (if he goes he'll only stay a couple years) then why not? They are a good side. It's a fine balance if it's worth it for a team like that though. Still cheaper than Torres or Carroll Report this comment (Comment number 141) Link to this (Comment number 141) He would waste the last important contract of his career in the Turkish league. God club but he needs to moderate his demands and will then be playing in Germany or England. Report this comment (Comment number 140) Link to this (Comment number 140) Comments 5 of 144Add your commentSign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20952917</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Michael Laudrup has hailed Swansea's 2-0 victory in the Capital One Cup semi-final first-leg over Chelsea as "very special", but insists his side still have a lot to do before they can think about the final. Don't Miss Match Report: Chelsea 0-2 SwanseaPlayer Ratings: Chelsea 0-2 SwanseaChelsea fans turn on Torres & BenitezChelsea lack long-term vision, says AVB Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Everton pound; 15.30 Draw pound; 37.50 Swansea City pound; 60.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Everton pound; 15.71 Draw pound; 40.00 Swansea City pound; 55.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Everton pound; 15.70 Draw pound; 40.00 Swansea City pound; 60.00 Both sides named strong teams during Wednesday night's Stamford Bridge clash, with the likes of Juan Mata and Eden Hazard starting for the hosts, although new signing Demba Ba had to settle for a place on the bench. The anonymous Fernando Torres received a notable amount of stick from the home support, while another Spaniard broke the deadlock for Swansea, as Michu grabbed his customary goal before Danny Graham wrapped up a win which left the manager delighted. Speaking to Sky Sports after the match, Laudrup said: "I think we had some historic results already this season, winning at Anfield and at the Emirates [Stadium], but of course winning an away game here, European champions from last season is obviously something very special. "I think obviously we knew it would be a difficult game. We had to defend a lot - much more than we're used to - but I think there are two parts of it. "Obviously the possession, they had much more possession than we had, that's obvious. But to be honest, after the game I watched the chances they had, and really they only had three big chances. They had Ramires first half, Mata, Luiz and then they had the goal disallowed offside. "It was offside. It was very tight but it was offside. "I think it was a marvellous fight. We are a team trying to play, but we know obviously when we go and play the European champions away we know we have to defend much more than we're used to. "To be honest I'm delighted with the result, I would lie if I said otherwise, but there's still a mountain to climb." Swansea's two goals both came as a result of defensive errors by Branislav Ivanovic, and although Laudrup recognises that, he highlighted that his players still needed to apply the finishes, which he is grateful they did. "It is true, they gave us two goals," he said. "But again you have to score them. Yeah two mistakes, but a part of that I think even if you take away our two goals they created three chances." Laudrup remained full of praise for Benitez's side, and was convinced that his team had to be perfect to prevent them scoring three or four times on the night. He continued: "This team we saw today [Chelsea], they have so many gifted players and so much quality. It depends on what we're doing on that day. "We have to play exactly the same, with the same intensity, everything, otherwise they can score three or four goals against us. "They can still win the semi-final, but of course it 's a great result and what I'm most happy about is we go into the second leg, playing at home in front of our crowd, full packed stadium with the possibility to go and play the final at Wembley. "I think that's best for me." Swansea 's star man this season, Michu, also spoke after the match and he hailed the work rate and energy of his teammates before explaining his goal. He said: "We worked very, very hard. I 'm very happy for the team, the key was the team worked very, very hard. "I saw De Guzman pressing the ball and I think: 'OK if it comes to my left foot I will shoot'. [But] The second leg will be very difficult." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/9/england/2013/01/09/3661023/laudrup-hails-very-special-chelsea-triumph-</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Antonio Conte praised the "great response" from his side after Juventus fought back to beat AC Milan 2-1 in the Coppa Italia quarter-final.
 Don't Miss Player Ratings: Juventus 2-1 Milan (aet)Match Report: Juventus 2-1 Milan (aet)Pirlo: Chelsea 'mad' to let Lampard leaveEXCL: Juve eye Muriel-Boakye swapEXCL: Juve join Milan in race for MugniDrogba's agent confirms Juve contact Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Parma pound; 52.50 Draw pound; 36.00 Juventus pound; 16.70 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Parma pound; 50.00 Draw pound; 35.00 Juventus pound; 17.27 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Parma pound; 50.00 Draw pound; 35.00 Juventus pound; 17.30 
Mirko Vucinic struck the winner in extra time after Sebastian Giovinco had levelled the match following Stephan El Shaarawy's early opener, and Conte was delighted that his charges were able to learn from their mistakes in their recent defeat to Sampdoria.

"It is always a tough game between these two great teams and clubs who have won so much," he told RAI after the match.

"Our hunger was huge and I received a great response from everyone, especially as I included many players who hadn 't featured for a while.

"I told them that what happened against Sampdoria must never happen again."

The 43-year-old reserved special praise for Marco Storari, who made a handful of impressive saves on the night as he deputised for Gianluigi Buffon.

"I compliment Marco Storari, as he played a great game in goal and I am very proud of him," he praised.

Man of the moment, Vucinic, was understandably elated after firing his team into the next round and hailed the efforts of the whole squad on the back of a disappointing weekend.

"All of us, all 13 or 14 players fought to win the game," the striker added.

"We didn't play as well as we could against Sampdoria, but we are fully focused on achieving all of our objectives." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/10/italy/2013/01/09/3660993/juventus-responded-as-i-had-hoped-says-conte</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Christophe Jallet has revealed his disappointment after Guillaume Hoarau left the Ligue 1 leaders for Dalian Aerbin on Wednesday.
 Don't Miss PSG do not fear Real Madrid, insists JalletJallet 'honoured' to play with IbraJallet: PSG can still improveHoarau admits PSG criticism is fair Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: PSG pound; 12.00 Draw pound; 60.00 AC Ajaccio pound; 150.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: PSG pound; 11.67 Draw pound; 65.00 AC Ajaccio pound; 150.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: PSG pound; 11.70 Draw pound; 70.00 AC Ajaccio pound; 150.00 
Hoarau, a full France international with five caps to his name, saw his role at Paris Saint-Germain diminish following the recruitment of several expensive forwards by coach Carlo Ancelotti.

Although the 28-year-old's exit was almost inevitable, Jallet admitted his departure was difficult to take after seeing his team-mate move all the way to China secure regular football.

"It is difficult for me because we were pretty close," he told TF1.

"China is his choice and it must be respected [but] we would have liked him not to go as far.

 "I have another point of view in that I would not want to live there." 

Hoarau will link up with former Barcelona midfielder Seydou Keita at his new club, based in the north-east province of Liaoning.
 ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/90/france/2013/01/09/3660932/jallet-upset-over-hoarau-departure</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ AC Milan vice-president Adriano Galliani has quashed reports linking the Italian giants with a move for Southampton's Gaston Ramirez. Don't Miss Gattuso tips Montella for AC MilanSanton dismisses Milan rumoursEXCL: Juve join Milan in race for MugniSaints set to sign Cagliari's Astori Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Sampdoria pound; 37.50 Draw pound; 33.00 Milan pound; 20.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Sampdoria pound; 36.00 Draw pound; 33.00 Milan pound; 20.50 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Sampdoria pound; 37.50 Draw pound; 32.50 Milan pound; 20.50 Saints signed Uruguay international Ramirez during the summer for a club record fee of &euro; 15 million from Bologna, but he is yet to live up to his billing after just three goals and no assists in 13 Premier League appearances - though injuries have hampered his progress. Milan are currently looking to add to their squad as they continue their rebuilding, but Galliani has ruled out a move for the Saints No.10, adding that expensive signings will only be brought in if other players are sold. Speaking to Sky Sports Italia, Galliani said: "There 's no need for Ramirez, we are fine as we are. If someone leaves then we 'll see, but there are no 'gifts' on the horizon for the fans." One player Milan do look poised to bring to San Siro is midfielder Riccardo Saponara, who is currently co-owned by Empoli and Parma. However, an agreement could be reached to purchase Empoli's half of the contract for around pound3m. "Saponara is certainly a player that fits in with the policy of focusing on youth that Milan are taking," Galliani noted. Fellow Serie A sides Juventus and Inter, as well as Liverpool are believed to be interested in the creative midfielder, but Empoli's director of sport as also confirmed Milan's interest. Speaking to Calciomercato, Marcello Carli said: "It's true, there is a deal with Milan for half of Saponara's contract. "He was tracked by many clubs, but the Rossoneri were quick off the blocks. The player will remain with us until the end of the season. That was a decisive factor in negotiations." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/11/transfer-zone/2013/01/09/3660935/galliani-insists-milan-are-not-inter</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Cristiano Ronaldo became the seventh highest scorer in Real Madrid's history as they defeated Celta Vigo 4-0 in the second leg of their Copa Del Rey round of 16 clash at Santiago Bernabeu on Wednesday. The Portuguese's hat-trick saw him move past Pirri in the club's all-time rankings with 174 goals, as los Blancos overcame a 2-1 first-leg deficit to progress by a 5-2 aggregate scoreline, and set up a quarter final date with Valencia. Ronaldo opened the scoring with a long-range effort two minutes into the match, and added his second on 24 minutes with a cool finish from close range to seemingly put the hosts in control. But Celta would come out of their shell in the second half, creating a number of chances as Madrid, dented by Sergio Ramos' 73rd minute red card, were forced to play the latter stages on the back foot. However, Ronaldo would put nerves around the Bernabeu to rest with his third goal minutes from the end, before Sami Khedira made it 4-0 on the stroke of injury time to finally seal the home side's passage into the next round. Jose Mourinho restored Iker Casillas to the starting lineup in place of Antonio Adan, with Ramos also returning to the centre of defence to displace Raphael Varane as the partner for Ricardo Carvalho. And Madrid needed only 90 seconds to eradicate their deficit, as Ronaldo punished a napping Celta defence with a stunning piledriver from outside the box that flew into the far corner. All the football was being played by the hosts, and it came as no surprise when they doubled their tally with 24 minutes on the clock. Ronaldo again made the breakthrough, latching onto a fantastic clipped pass from Luka Modric to bury a cool, one-touch finish into the net. Karim Benzema could have made it 3-0 on the night just before the half-hour mark when he took aim from an unmarked position inside the box, but he could only place his shot within the grasp of Sergio. And the Celta stopper was called into action again minutes later to stop a goalbound Mesut Ozil shot with his legs, after the German international had initially looked to have rounded the keeper for a tap in. Sergio was kept busy for the remainder of the half, but came up with a brilliant double save on Karim Benzema from point blank range to keep Celta in the hunt heading into the break. The visitors were certainly improved in the second-half, and Park Chu Young nearly brought them back into the game after coming within inches of turning home a dangerous cross by Enrique De Lucas, who then tested Casillas with a rasping drive from just inside the box. Celta were looking increasingly dangerous, and Ramos would ensure a tense ending to the game when he departed with his second yellow card, given after kicking out at Augusto Fernandez, an incident which could have warranted a straight red on its own. The visitors looked to sieze the initiative, and twice forced the very best out of Casillas with a pair of testing efforts from Michael Krohn-Dehli and Agusto Fernandez in the last ten minutes. But Ronaldo would finally end Celta's brave challenge in the 88th minute after clinically finishing off a counterattack, before Khedira rounded off matters at the death with a deft shot after manouvering into space inside the area. Madrid will now ready themselves for a quarter-final clash against Liga rivals Valencia, with the first leg set to take place at the Bernabeu on January 15. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/12/spain/2013/01/09/3660676/real-madrid-4-0-celta-vigo-agg-5-2-clinical-</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Trial ... Bernie Ibini to trial with Club Brugge. Source: Tracey Nearmy / AAP Central Coast Mariners could be set to lose another young star with striker Bernie Ibini headed abroad for a trial at Belgian heavyweights Club Brugge. Ibini will travel to Belgium on Sunday to link up with the Jupiler Pro League side after the Mariners' clash with Melbourne Victory in Tasmania. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Club Brugge extended the trial invitation to Ibini and the Mariners overnight, with the 20-year-old expressing his eagerness to explore the opportunity, the club says.The pacey forward will now miss next Saturday's F3 Derby with Newcastle at Bluetongue Stadium, but is due to return from the 10-day trial in time for the Mariners' round 18 clash with high-flying Adelaide United.Ibini, who has scored 11 goals in his 49 appearances since making his senior debut at the Mariners in 2010, is under contract with the club until the end of the 2013/14 season. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player. Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.But should the Mariners receive a worthwhile offer from the Belgian side he could be gone as early as next month.The January transfer window could wreak havoc on the table-topping Mariners' championship hopes with playmaker Tomas Rogic, who is off contract at the end of this season, flying out to Spain on Thursday for a trial at Scottish Premier League side Celtic.Meanwhile, boom goalkeeper Mat Ryan, also a free agent after this season, has had his trial with Scottish fourth-tier club Rangers postponed due to a shoulder injury.]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/central-coast-mariners-striker-bernie-ibini-to-trial-with-belgi</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Three for me ... Cristiano Ronaldo scores another stunning hat-trick for Madrid. Source: Daniel Ochoa De Olza / AFP Cristiano Ronaldo responded to missing out on the Ballon d'Or by hitting a stunning hat-trick in Real Madrid's 4-0 defeat of Celta Vigo to reach the Spanish Cup soccer quarter-finals. Trailing 2-1 from the first leg of their last-16 tie, Portuguese star Ronaldo struck twice early before settling the outcome with three minutes remaining to calm his team's nerves after Sergio Ramos had been sent off with 17 minutes to go.Sami Khedira added the fourth in the final minute and Jose Mourinho's men will meet Valencia in the next round before a potential semi-final tie with eternal rivals Barcelona who knocked Madrid out last season at the quarter-final stage.Mourinho recalled goalkeeper Iker Casillas for the clash after he had controversially dropped the club captain to the bench for the past two La Liga games.Ronaldo, beaten to the Ballon d'Or by Lionel Messi, hit a sensational opener after only two minutes.Receiving the ball from a short throw-in, the Portuguese hit an unstoppable shot from wide on the left that fizzed and then bent before beating Sergio in the Celta goal at his far post.It was the same man who hit a shot over the bar from long range 10 minutes later, before he doubled his side's lead with one delicate touch on 23 minutes to finish off a Luka Modric through ball.Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.The pressure increased for Madrid when Ramos was dismissed for his second yellow card and Casillas had to make important saves from Michael Krohn-Dehli and Augusto Fernandez before Ronaldo scored his third with a crisp shot from the left to ease nerves on 87 minutes before Khedira made it four.]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/cristiano-ronaldo-scores-stunning-hat-trick-as-real-madrid-ease</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Source: FOX SPORTS Fox Sports football commentator Mel McLaughlin previews round 16 of the A-League season and gives you her tips for every game. A-League Ladder P W D L GD Pts 1 Central Coast 15 10 3 2 15 33 2 Adelaide 15 9 2 4 7 29 3 Victory 15 8 2 5 0 26 4 Western Sydney 15 7 2 6 4 23 5 Perth 15 5 4 6 2 19 6 Heart 15 5 3 7 -2 18 7 Brisbane 15 5 2 8 0 17 8 Newcastle 15 5 2 8 -9 17 9 Wellington 15 4 4 7 -3 16 10 Sydney 15 4 2 9 -14 14 Round 15 - as at 00:00 AM, 06/01/13 Round 15 - as at 00:00 AM, 06/01/13Adelaide United v Perth Glory, Friday, 7.30pm (EDT), Hindmarsh Stadium

Why you should watch itNeither of these two negotiated the Christmas/New Year period all that successfully. Adelaide picked up four points from a possible 12 while Perth managed just five points from their four matches. Remarkably, 10 points separates the sides. Perth led Sydney twice last weekend before eventually succumbing to a draw. That won't sit well. The positive was the return to form of Shane Smeltz. The Reds will have expected to do better at Hunter Stadium last weekend but a 0-0 draw in oppressive heat isn 't the worst result. Goalkeeper Eugene Galekovic continues to be one of the stars of the league, pulling off some spectacular saves to keep his team in the match. Adelaide have struggled of late when pressed high by their opponents, and Friday night should be no different. There 's a fierce rivalry here and it 'll be physical as well.Key menGalekovic, Dario Vidosic, Bruce Djite. Adelaide are so strong up front but they need to start scoring again.Who will win? Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.You get the sense Glory may be getting back on track, and not a moment too soon if they are to achieve anything close to what they did last season. The signs were there against Sydney and letting the lead slip twice might be just be what spurs them to victory here. A-League Round 16 Friday, January 11 Adelaide Adelaide vs Perth 7:30 PM Hindmarsh Stadium Perth Saturday, January 12 Victory Victory vs Central Coast 5:30 PM Aurora Stadium Central Coast Newcastle Newcastle vs Brisbane 7:45 PM Hunter Stadium Brisbane Sunday, January 13 Wellington Wellington vs Western Sydney 2:30 PM Westpac Stadium Western Sydney Sydney Sydney vs Heart 5:00 PM Allianz Stadium Heart All times are listed in EDT Melbourne Victory v Central Coast Mariners, Saturday, 5.30pm (EDT), Aurora Stadium, LauncestonI still think Victory are the biggest threat to the Mariners this season. Collecting all three points at Parramatta Stadium last weekend was a big result for Central Coast. And to do it without star play-maker Tom Rogic and captain John Hutchinson, who started from the bench, was even more meritorious. Victory got back on track against Wellington Phoenix. Marco Rojas and Archie Thompson continue to be a formidable pairing up front while Marcos Flores, who admitted he was low on confidence, is slowly coming around. Significantly, Adama Traore was the man of the match last weekend. The better the defenders get the scarier the prospect Victory becomes. They could not be separated in their last encounter in one of the best A-League games to date. Graham Arnold and Ange Postecoglou are mates but this will count for little come kick off. The sideline will be a tense place to be!Key men A big job for both backlines, how to contain Rojas, McBreen, and Thompson. An exciting prospect.Who will win?Some big games this weekend, but this is my match of the round - and again I can 't separate these two. Draw. Alex Tobin Award 3,2,1 Points Check in every week for the latest points handed out in the A-League's Alex Tobin Award. + 6 &lt;/p&gt; Best: Alex Tobin Award points tally + 14 Check in every week for the latest points handed out in the A-League's Alex Tobin Award.Newcastle Jets v Brisbane Roar, Saturday, 7.45pm (EDT), Hunter StadiumBoth teams are locked on 17 points - just one point out of the six - so there is everything to play for. Newcastle looked to be in for a tough day at the office last weekend but a mid-half drinks break gave them the chance to tighten things up. It was their first clean-sheet of the season. And for all the tinkering Gary van Egmond has done so far, both forced and tactically, he may now want to persist with this youthful backline. Brisbane lost - again - to Melbourne Heart, but can take some comfort from their second-half fightback. They dominated possession once again but were slow to convert territory into real threats. Their reliance on Besart Berisha must be of real concern. Great news for Roar with the addition of Jade North in defence but he won 't feature this week. The Jets have some injury concerns and they will be relieved Ruben Zadkovich did not suffer a major knee injury this week.Key menThomas Broich and Mitch Nichols need to find their goalscoring boots to help back-up star striker Besart Berisha. This may be a great chance to score some goals.Who will win?I 'm expecting an entertaining match but can 't tip against Brisbane, especially up against a relatively-inexperienced defence. A-League Video A-League Highlights Catch up with all the great video highlights from the latest round of Hyundai A-League action. &lt;/p&gt; Match Highlights: All the round nine action Catch up with all the great video highlights from the latest round of Hyundai A-League action.Wellington Phoenix v Western Sydney Wanderers, Sunday, 2.30pm (EDT), Westpac StadiumWellington's season is very much on the line here. They 've lost seven of their 15 fixtures so far and continue to struggle defensively. Wanderers went down to the table-topping Mariners to slip to fourth but still have a handy four-point buffer on fifth-placed Perth. It 's worth noting the Wanderers have lost just one game fewer than Phoenix but their seven victories keep them well in the mix. Phoenix worked hard to contain Melbourne Victory last weekend but defensive mistakes cost them, and they were unable to maintain their intensity for 90 minutes. Even though key men Paul Ifill and Manny Muscat are missing, coach Ricky Herbert insists he will not change his approach. But as frustration grows among fans, and the team for that matter, they must take the points here. Jeremy Brockie did the damage last time the two sides met and he will be crucial again.Key playerShinji Ono continues to be the key for Wanderers. He would have scored against the Mariners if not for a fantastic goal-line clearance from Pedj Bojic. The danger man.Who will win?Have to go on form here but Wanderers, who have been resilient on the road, will face a pretty desperate opponent. Western Sydney to win. Bozza's Review A-League Round 15 Fox Sports' Mark Bosnich dissects an exciting round 15 of A-League action. + 22 &lt;/p&gt; Review: 'Victory have firepower to win it all' + 22 Fox Sports' Mark Bosnich dissects an exciting round 15 of A-League action.Sydney FC v Melbourne Heart, Sunday, 5pm (EDT), Allianz StadiumFrank Farina has described his team 's next two matches as "season-defining", and I think that should also apply to their opponents on Sunday. There were promising signs for both teams last weekend. Sydney came from behind twice to draw in Perth with Jason Culina getting on the scoresheet. Heart, meanwhile, fought off a second-half onslaught to take all three points against Brisbane. But if neither side can find consistency in a hurry then it 's hard to see them featuring in April. Sydney will again be forced to field a make-shift backline - although left-back Fabio could return, as should striker Yairo Yau, after both trained well during the week. New signing Joel Griffiths will remain in the stands for another week. Culina has become as important as Alessandro del Piero and their hunger and leadership on the field sets the tone.Key menRichard Garcia and Josip Tadic are key figures for the red and whites, and it was good to see captain Fred chipping in with a goal.Who will win?A big evening at Allianz Stadium is assured. Sydney, because it is a must-win and a big test of character, to win, but it will be close.]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/a-league/fox-sports-football-commentator-mel-mclaughlin-preview</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Uncertainty ... will Evan Kostopoulos and Iain Ramsay be around in Adelaide next season? Source: News Limited Iain Fyfe is on the verge of extending his Adelaide United contract, leaving three out of five of the Reds' remaining off-contract players fighting for spots for next season. It seems that Iain Ramsay and Zenon Caravella will be dicing for just one contract, if the pair hasn't already made plans to move to other clubs during the long A-League off-season. A-League Round 16 Friday, January 11 Adelaide Adelaide vs Perth 7:30 PM Hindmarsh Stadium Perth Saturday, January 12 Victory Victory vs Central Coast 5:30 PM Aurora Stadium Central Coast Newcastle Newcastle vs Brisbane 7:45 PM Hunter Stadium Brisbane Sunday, January 13 Wellington Wellington vs Western Sydney 2:30 PM Westpac Stadium Western Sydney Sydney Sydney vs Heart 5:00 PM Allianz Stadium Heart All times are listed in EDT After Adelaide chairman Greg Griffin confirmed it had signed youth players Awer Mabil, 17, and Jordan Elsey, 18, on professional contracts, the club has now secured 20 signatures for next season.Given the salary cap stays in place for next season with no collective bargaining agreement beyond April 30, only three spots remain under the current 23-man squad agreement.Griffin said new contracts won't be announced until the end of the season but it's understood Fyfe is close to agreeing to a new contract term. Griffin also confirmed striker Serginho van Dijk would not be at the club next season. A-League Ladder P W D L GD Pts 1 Central Coast 15 10 3 2 15 33 2 Adelaide 15 9 2 4 7 29 3 Victory 15 8 2 5 0 26 4 Western Sydney 15 7 2 6 4 23 5 Perth 15 5 4 6 2 19 6 Heart 15 5 3 7 -2 18 7 Brisbane 15 5 2 8 0 17 8 Newcastle 15 5 2 8 -9 17 9 Wellington 15 4 4 7 -3 16 10 Sydney 15 4 2 9 -14 14 Round 15 - as at 00:00 AM, 06/01/13 Round 15 - as at 00:00 AM, 06/01/13Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.That leaves Caravella, Ramsay, Evan Kostopoulos and Fabian Barbiero dicing for the remaining spots if Teeboy Kamara (ill) remains on the new-season roster.Kostopoulos and Barbiero are well positioned to earn contracts, given the pair are locals and would save the club money on expenses accommodation and transport."We're not in discussions until the end of the season," Griffin said."Apart from that, every uncontracted player had a contract put in front of them."Those who accepted it have re-signed and those who didn't accept it we've put off until the end of the year."Now we have to sit and work out how we're going to fit in two more."]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/a-league/five-reds-are-vying-for-three-remaining-contracts/stor</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Hello, you either have JavaScript turned off or an old version of Adobe's Flash Player.Stunned ... Fernando Torres and Juan Mata react to Michu's opener. Source: Matt Dunham / AFP Two horrible Branislav Ivanovic errors gave Swansea a huge advantage in their Capital One Cup semi-final with Chelsea after a 2-0 first-leg win at Stamford Bridge The defender's failure to control a ball on the edge of his own penalty area gave Michu the chance to open the scoring in the first half against the run of play.Chelsea, who started with Fernando Torres instead of January signing Demba Ba, dominated but Danny Graham made it 2-0 in injury time when pouncing on Ivanovic's blind back-pass.The European champions had a claim for a penalty, which saw Ba booked for diving, immediately before Graham's goal but they must now overcome two away goals in the second leg.But interim boss Benitez heard his team booed off at the final whistle and they must now overcome two away goals in the second leg.Chelsea's fans spent a large chunk of the match berating Benitez for his failure to bring on Ba, who scored twice on debut last weekend, and they also took umbrage with the interim boss' failure to bring on Frank Lampard until the 70th minute.The Blues dominated the game, but lacked a killer touch up front and they paid the price in the 39th minute when Ivanovic's blunder gifted Michu the chance to score his 16th goal of the season.Start of sidebar. Skip to end of sidebar.End of sidebar. Return to start of sidebar.Ba was sent on in place of Torres in the 81st minute and hurtled through injury time and went down after Gerhard Tremmel failed to collect the ball in the penalty are but the referee did not give a penalty and instead booked the former Newcastle United man for diving.Chelsea's night then turned from bad to worse with one minute of added time left. Ivanovic's second terrible back-pass allowed Graham to pinch the ball off Turnbull before slotting in to an empty net.Read more: http://www1.skysports.com/football/live/match/280792/report]]></content>
 <link>http://www.foxsports.com.au/football/swansea-city-stun-chelsea-with-2-0-victory-in-first-leg-of-leag</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Home Y! Sports Experts Y! Sports Blogs Photo Galleries Rivals.com Video Y! Sports Radio Action Sports NFL NFL Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video NFL This Week Fantasy Football Fantasy 101 Fantasy Football Live Survival Football Outside the Game Blog Picks Tickets MLB MLB Home News Y! Sports Experts Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Injuries Odds Video Big League Stew Tickets Playoffs NBA NBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video NBA Highlights Video Coverage Featured Plays On Point Ball Don't Lie News Tickets NHL NHL Home Puck Daddy News Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Odds Video Photos Tickets NCAAF Home News Previews Recaps Scores & Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Boards Video Road To Saturday Blog Picks Odds Tickets NCAAB NCAAB Home News Previews Recaps Scores and Schedules Standings Rankings Recruiting Stats Team Sites Message Board Odds Video Blog Tickets NASCAR NASCAR Home Schedule and Results Standings Stats Drivers Tracks Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Truck Series Nationwide Series Fantasy Photos From The Marbles Tickets News Head2Head Golf Golf Home Pro Tours Schedule Stats Players Leaderboard Video Video Coverage Highlights Features Nationwide Photos Devil Ball Golf Instruction Equipment Courses/Travel Tickets UFC MMA Home Rankings Schedule Video Photos Cagewriter Twitter Tickets UFC PPV: UFC 155 Boxing Boxing Home Rankings Results Schedule Champions Video Photos Blog Tickets Soccer More Rivals.com Rivals High Rivals High Home Prep Rally News Message Boards High School BCS Rivals High TV Olympics Home Schedule Fourth-Place Medal Photos Team Mom Beijing 2008 Vancouver 2010 MLS MLS Home Schedule Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets Tennis Tennis Home Rankings Matches Schedule Players Video Busted Racquet Photos Tickets NCAAW NCAAW Home Scores and Schedules Rankings Standings Stats Teams Photos News Previews Recaps WNBA WNBA Home Scores and Schedules Standings Stats Teams Players Transactions Photos Cycling Cycling Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog IndyCar IndyCar Home Standings Schedule Video Photos CFL (CA) Horse Racing Horse Racing Home Video Photos SB Nation Blog Winter Sports Winter Sports Home Photos Skiing Schedule Results: Men Results: Women Standings: Men Standings: Women Investigations ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Fantasy GamesFootball Basketball Hockey Pro Pick'em Bowl Pick'em Golf Sports IQ World Soccer Home MLS Fixtures Standings Teams Players Injuries Tickets England Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Spain Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Italy Fixtures and Results Weekly Report History Germany Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Netherlands Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History France Fixtures & Results Weekly Report History Team USA Dirty Tackle Discover Yahoo! With Your Friends Loginclose PREVIEW-Soccer-Van Persie and Suarez set for Old Trafford shoot-outBy Martyn Herman | Reuters - 6 hours ago Email 0 Recommend 0 Tweet 0 LONDON, Jan 10 (Reuters) - Robin van Persie and Luis Suarez's tussle at the top of the Premier League goalscoring charts continues at Old Trafford on Sunday as leaders Manchester United take on Liverpool in one of the season's most keenly-anticipated fixtures. Neither player can stop scoring but while the superlatives have rained down on 16-goal Dutchman Van Persie, Suarez's 15 have more often than not been accompanied with pantomime-villain antics that polarise opinion on the Uruguayan. Last weekend proved a typical scenario as the FA Cup briefly took centre stage after a barrage of holiday Premier League action which left United seven points clear of title rivals Manchester City, who face Arsenal on Sunday. Van Persie's last-gasp equaliser against West Ham United had purists salivating but 24 hours later Suarez's integrity was called into question after he got away with a blatant handball to score his side's second goal against minor-league Mansfield. While van Persie has proved to be worth every penny of the 24 million pounds ($38.49 million) United paid Arsenal for his services, Suarez's contribution to a Liverpool side finally flourishing under Brendan Rodgers after a terrible start is perhaps even more impressive. He has worked tirelessly as a lone striker for most of the campaign and while his antics and reputation for diving mean the snipers will always be aiming for him, he is establishing himself as the latest idol on Liverpool's famous Kop. At least the 160th league clash between the fierce north west rivals looks like being spared the controversial build-up which has marred their most recent meetings. The focus before and during United's 2-1 victory at Liverpool in September was on concerns about crowd behaviour in the wake of the publication of a report into the Hillsborough disaster that claimed 96 Liverpool fans and spawned several sickening songs from United fans. Last February at Old Trafford the match was overshadowed by the continuing racism row between the clubs following Suarez's eight-match ban for calling United's Patrice Evra "negro" - a situation inflamed by Suarez's refusal to shake hands with the Frenchman before kickoff. United manager Alex Ferguson labelled Suarez "a disgrace" at the time but on Sunday he will be more concerned with making sure his leaky defence keeps the south American quiet. Suarez, who has admirably led the Liverpool attack alone this season now has Daniel Sturridge for company after he joined from Chelsea. Both scored against Mansfield although how to pair them successfully could pose a challenge to Rodgers who has hinted that Suarez may be moved to a wider position. "When he played at Ajax he played in behind as a number 10, in between the lines, and he played as a reverse winger from the left side so he wasn't quite out wide - he was tucked in round the corner," Rodgers said this week. "Wherever he plays he will make the same movements and he will find the space because he is a world class player." Both United and Liverpool have scored 11 goals in their last four league matches with United showing no sign of missing Wayne Rooney who is still a major doubt for Sunday with a knee injury. Manchester City will be hoping Liverpool can do them a favour although three points against Arsenal at the Emirates will be a tall order for Roberto Mancini's side especially as midfield powerhouse Yaya Toure is preparing for the African Cup of Nations with Ivory Coast. City lost 1-0 at Arsenal in April last year when Mario Balotelli was sent off, although they recovered from what seemed like a knockout blow for their title hopes to surge past United in the most dramatic ever finish to a Premier League season. Balotelli was involved in a training ground bust-up with Mancini last week and although the two volatile Italians appear to have made up, it would be a surprise if Balotelli earns himself a starting slot in north London. Arsenal are playing catch-up in the battle for a top-four place having fallen four points behind fourth-placed Chelsea. After scoring twice on his debut in the FA Cup at Southampton last week Demba Ba could make his first league start for Chelsea as they try to penetrate Stoke City's rock-like defence on Saturday. Third-placed Tottenham Hotspur can move to within three points of Manchester City if they win at bottom club Queens Park Rangers on Saturday although they will be up against former manager Harry Redknapp as he continues his latest Houdini act following their 1-0 win at Chelsea last week. ($1 = 0.6235 British pounds) (Reporting by Martyn Herman; editing by Toby Davis) @yahoosports on Twitter, become a fan on Facebook Explore Related Content1 - 4 of 20prev next Britain Soccer Premier League Soccer-Missing out on Van Persie has hurt &hellip;LONDON, Jan 1 (Reuters) - Robin van Persie's decision to join Manchester United instead of Manchester &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;Soccer-Missing out on Van Persie has hurt City, says Mancini Reuters Robin Van Persie UPDATE 2-Soccer-Van Persie shines again as &hellip;(Adds details, quotes, byline) * Van Persie and Hernandez at the double in 4-0 win at Wigan * Man City &hellip; Full Story &#xBB;UPDATE 2-Soccer-Van Persie shines again as United march on Reuters Katherine Webb didn&#x2019;t see any need for ESPN apology about Brent Musburger&#x2019;s commentsOregon&#x2019;s &#x2018;Rudy&#x2019; gets into Fiesta Bowl thanks to teammate faking an injuryMaloofs nearing deal to sell Kings to group that plans to relocate franchise to SeattleAJ McCarron, girlfriend Katherine Webb enjoying limelight after fixation sparks Internet fervorNo one will be admitted to the Hall of Fame from the writer&#x2019;s ballot this seasonTexas A&M OT Luke Joeckel declares for 2013 NFL draft, could be first overall pickMark Cuban was fined for tweeting about officials, raising new questionsRobert Griffin III has surgery to repair the LCL, ACL in right kneeHe's more than just your average fanCollapse of famous arch caught on cameraDramatic photos show family fleeing firesFirst-ever glimpse of giant squid in the wildRunaway bulls chase police officersWhite House rules on Morgan deportationAl Gore's staggering personal fortuneWait, that's actually a Burger King? Yahoo! SportsHome NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy More Yahoo! Sports &#xBB; Also On Yahoo!Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert All Yahoo! &#xBB; Trending NowBody of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks Home NFL MLB NBA NHL NCAAF NCAAB NASCAR Golf UFC Boxing Soccer More ThePostGame Shop Fantasy Autos Finance Games Groups Health Maps Movies Music News omg! Shine Shopping Sports Travel TV Y! News RSS Y! News Alert Body of mom found in trunk Redskins name change Katt Williams arrested Sol Yurick dies Piers Morgan deportation 5 new Apple products McClain arrested for signature Clooney and Crawford Bieber-Gomez split Stocks (c) Copyright Thomson Reuters 2013. Click For Restrictions - http://about.reuters.com/fulllegal.asp Copyright &#xA9; 2013 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved. | Yahoo! - ABC News Network | Help / Suggestions Privacy Policy About Our Ads Terms of Service Copyright/IP Policy ]]></content>
 <link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/sports/rss/sow/SIG=136h9j4hj/*http%3A//sports.yahoo.com/news/preview-soccer-v</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[The good and the bad of Beckham 9 January 2013 Last updated at 12:49 GMT David Beckham is considering offers from Europe, Asia, the Middle East and South America, but will base his family in London wherever he ends up. The former England captain has been living in Los Angeles since 2007 but will move after leaving LA Galaxy. Beckham, 37, will hold a series of meetings with his advisors next week as he nears a decision about his future. However, French Ligue 2 side Monaco are understood to have ended their interest in the midfielder after holding talks. The former Manchester United and Real Madrid player ended his five-and-a-half-year stint at LA Galaxy in December. The schooling of Beckham's four children is a priority but he is still weighing up offers from various continents. Beckham joined Manchester United as a 14-year-old and went on to make 398 appearances for the club, winning six Premier League titles and the Champions League. He moved to Real Madrid in a &#xA3;25m deal in 2003 and won the La Liga title in 2007 before joining LA Galaxy. Beckham won the MLS Cup twice during his time in America and his last match was the 2012 MLS Cup final, where he helped his side beat Houston Dynamo 3-1. The midfielder, who made his England debut against Moldova in 1996 and captained the side from 2000 to 2006, made his 115th and final appearance for the national side in a 3-0 win against Belarus in 2009. He was at Upton Park on Saturday as West Ham drew 2-2 with Manchester United in the FA Cup third round, but Hammers boss Sam Allardyce would not be drawn on potential interest in signing Beckham. French side Paris Saint-Germain have expressed an interest in signing Beckham, who has also been linked with moves to Russia, China, Australia and Brazil. Beckham is expected to decide his playing future next week. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20957090</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 16:34 GMT Players' union chief Gordon Taylor says the Football Association's &#xA3;18,000-a-year contract offer to England's top women players is "embarrassing". Hope Powell's squad have decided not to sign their central contracts after advice from the Professional Footballers' Association (PFA). Taylor says the offer does not reflect the popularity of the women's game. "Come on, that figure is embarrassing. Top Premier League players are earning more in a day," he said. Head coach: Hope Powell Captain: Casey Stoney Most caps: Rachel Yankey (121) Top scorer: Kelly Smith (45) Fifa ranking: Eighth The PFA is seeking to reach an agreement with the FA as England women's previous &#xA3;16,000-a-year deal ended in November and players went unpaid last month. It is understood that negotiations between the PFA and FA centre around the additional 24 hours players are allowed to work each week in addition to players' central contracts and money they receive on a semi-professional basis from their clubs. England have qualified for Euro 2013 in Sweden while the 2012 Olympics proved a big hit with fans, more than 70,000 turning out at Wembley for the GB women's win over Brazil. Taylor said: "I am surprised the FA have not been more responsive to the girls' reasonable demand. "In some ways, [the FA] have done a lot for the women's game, which now has increased TV coverage and obviously the facility at St George's Park [the recently opened FA centre of excellence in Burton] is available for both male and female players. "But they are offering to move these central contracts up from &#xA3;16,000, which has been the figure since 2009, to &#xA3;18,000." Some players have to take part-time jobs to supplement their income, but training demands for club and country mean players cannot always find employment that offers enough flexibility. England and Lincoln Ladies defender Sophie Bradley told the BBC: "I think it's now got to the point where we need to be rewarded because of the amount of people who are interested in watching us play and the progression of the game." The squad is at St George's Park for fitness testing before flying to La Manga in Spain on Sunday for a week-long training camp. Sign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. All posts are reactively-moderated
 and must obey the house rules Women expect men to pay for their sport provide the officialdom (over 80% of officials are male!) provide their coaching. Equality means "I'll take what I want at your expense". Why is women's football an unmitigated fail and can not stand on its own 2 feet? Don't see any successful business women stepping forward to act as benefactor and that is your answer: take take take. Report this comment (Comment number 304) Link to this (Comment number 304) Who actually watches womans football? 16 grand for kicking a ball about a field is pretty good in my opinion. Men get paid more because the game is one million times more valuable commercially Report this comment (Comment number 303) Link to this (Comment number 303) I think womens football has come on over the last few years, but the amount offered is about what it is worth commercially. The standard is generally very average and with the exception of the ageing Kelly Smith, the game in this country has produced very few household names. Gordon Taylor is a total prat, if he is so concerned, fund the extra from The PFA's huge resources. Report this comment (Comment number 302) Link to this (Comment number 302) I don't understand, if they are so "in love" with playing football why don't they play for &#xA3;0 a week, they clearly only want the money so they aren't much different from the men at all, so no womens is not much better than the mens Report this comment (Comment number 301) Link to this (Comment number 301) Add sexism to the problems of racism & homophobia that the FA faces ... Report this comment (Comment number 300) Link to this (Comment number 300) Comments 5 of 304Add your commentSign in with your BBC iD, or Register to comment and rate comments All posts are reactively-moderated and must obey the house rules. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20962988</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[Jose Mourinho 9 January 2013 Last updated at 15:08 GMT A survey of Real Madrid fans has suggested that supporters may be losing faith in coach Jose Mourinho. Pro-Real Madrid Spanish sports newspaper Marca surveyed 704 supporters before last Sunday's win against Real Sociedad. While 54.4% said Mourinho should stay next season, 41.8% said it was time for him to go. Two-thirds of fans polled said the former Chelsea boss's actions were damaging the club's image. The supporters gave his performance as coach an average mark of 6.68 out of 10, down from 8.82 in March 2011. Real are 16 points behind arch-rivals Barcelona in Spain's La Liga. Former Porto, Chelsea and Inter Milan coach Mourinho, 49, was jeered when his name was read out before kick-off against Real Sociedad on Sunday. The Portuguese angered many supporters after dropping club legend Iker Casillas for the second game in a row. The goalkeeper's replacement, Antonio Adan, was sent-off after just six minutes of the match. Mourinho vowed not to leave his post following a 3-2 defeat to Malaga in December, saying: "I'm not worried at all and I'm not going to resign. I'm not a child, I know that results count." ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20960987</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 13:32 GMT West Ham co-chairman David Gold is in hospital suffering from pneumonia. The 76-year-old, who spent several days in hospital in 2011 with septicaemia, is on strong antibiotics, said his daughter Jacqueline. "My dad had a good night but is still on strong medication for his condition," she said on Twitter. "He is still very poorly but in good hands and obviously won't be at the game [at Sunderland] on Saturday." He attended West Ham's 2-2 home draw with Manchester United on Saturday but was taken to hospital by his daughter on Tuesday night. She tweeted on Tuesday: "I think he's learnt a very harsh lesson - not to go to football with bronchitis, he now has pneumonia. He is being assessed." Gold and co-chairman David Sullivan, who had previously been owners of Birmingham City, took over the east London club in January 2010. Gold was in hospital in February 2011 with septicaemia and cholangitis - inflammation of the bile duct - but made a full recovery. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20960790</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ 9 January 2013 Last updated at 16:42 GMT Sunderland have completed the signing of Bursaspor midfielder Alfred N'Diaye, 22, on a three-and-a-half-year contract, for an undisclosed fee. N'Diaye, who can also play in defence, spent three years with French club Nancy before moving to Turkey in 2011. The France Under-21 international could feature against West Ham on Saturday, subject to international clearance. "He is a powerful young player and can offer us more strength in depth," said Sunderland boss Martin O'Neill. "He will give us options and I'm delighted we have been able to bring him to the club." Sunderland are 14th in the Premier League, four points above the relegation zone, and have conceded five goals in their last two league games. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20962396</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ COMMENT
By Jay Jaffa

It seems remarkably unprofessional on a club and player level that Emmanuel Adebayor will be allowed to flee north London for South Africa next week for the Africa Cup of Nations, but regardless of which party you feel is most responsible, it leaves Tottenham in an arduous position after a summer of neglect last year.
 Don't Miss Adebayor to represent Togo at AfconSpurs starlets must be patient - FreundSherwood challenges Fryers to improveDamiao not your typical Brazilian strikerSpurs to make official &#x20AC;18m Damiao bidHoltby excited by Tottenham move Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: QPR pound; 42.00 Draw pound; 34.00 Tottenham pound; 18.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: QPR pound; 43.33 Draw pound; 35.00 Tottenham pound; 18.33 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: QPR pound; 43.30 Draw pound; 36.00 Tottenham pound; 18.30 
The vigorous one-eyed pursuit for Adebayor between seasons felt strange, particularly after the appointment of Andre Villas-Boas. The Togolese striker had played his best football for years in last season's fourth-place campaign under Harry Redknapp and was a popular member of the squad, but was he the right fit for Villas-Boas? 

With Daniel Levy, the Spurs chairman, overseeing Tottenham's summer transfer business, it hardly mattered. 

The fallout from an unhappy time at the Etihad Stadium left Manchester City looking to sell for peanuts and Levy salivating at the prospect of securing an impossibly cheap deal from the Premier League champions. The deal was done and initially it seemed a wise move - he had after all, contributed 17 goals and 11 assists in the league, the fourth highest combined contribution.

But reports of an early season disagreement suggested Adebayor had not warmed as much to Villas-Boas as he did to Redknapp's arm-round-the-shoulder approach and recent evidence suggests this relationship is set to deteriorate further. 

He hardly endeared himself to the club by spending a sizable portion of the summer in the United States, returning to Tottenham woefully out of shape and short of fitness. By the time he was deemed ready to contribute to the first-team, Adebayor looked off the pace, overweight and quickly picked up an injury. 
 ADE-BYE-OR
 ADEBAYOR IN 2011-12
 GAMES PLAYED
GOALS
ASSISTS
 37
18
12
 ADEBAYOR'S 2012-13 SO FAR
 GAMES PLAYED
GOALS
ASSISTS
 17
4
0
 
Fast forward to the present day and although he started the last six league games, scoring once, as part of a 4-4-2, he will jet off to the Africa Cup of Nations after Saturday's match at QPR, despite initially informing the club and his nation that he would boycott the tournament on account of unpaid bonuses and the absence of security promises. 

Further still, after Villas-Boas' public claims that he would not stand in Adebayor's way, the striker told the Togolese Football Federation: "So that 's what he told the press, but this is not what he told me. There is a difference between what is said face to face and what is said to the press. So I will go there and I will discuss it with Daniel Levy after I get back."

In the cold light of day, his U-turn is hugely unprofessional and puts the ambitions of the White Hart Lane outfit in jeopardy, as well as having the makings of the first spat between Adebayor and the club. That said, this brings us to the wider and far more long-running debate about the manner of Tottenham's transfer dealings.

In signing Adebayor and allowing Louis Saha to leave the club after a six-month spell, Levy, Villas-Boas and everyone working behind the scenes would have been aware of the possibility that the 28-year-old would be unavailable for a portion of the season (if Togo reach the final, he will miss four league games and one FA Cup tie). In fact, everyone in the stands, armchairs and on forums would have seen this scenario coming months ago. 

Tottenham are in a mess. It may only be temporary, but the league is as finely balanced as it has been in the Premier League era (if you discount the two Manchester teams) and dropped points in this period could well prove damaging when the final scores are totted up in May. 

Jermain Defoe will be the club's only senior striker for almost a month (Clint Dempsey may be labelled a striker by the manager and coaches, but that is merely PR spin), and the more cynical supporters will be expecting an injury to sideline the 30-year-old as soon as Adebayor disappears. 

Defoe has netted just one league goal since he was regularly partnered with Adebayor, which may, perversely, give fans hope, if Spurs return to Villas-Boas' preferred 4-2-3-1. Prolific in the opening stages of the season, Defoe confounded those who expected him to be marginalised by a new more intricate system. Perhaps Tottenham will see the best of Defoe he is asked to carry the goalscoring burden once more.

But that detracts from the point. In this instance Levy should be made accountable for the neglect of the squad, particularly if it costs Spurs points in the coming weeks. Providing Villas-Boas with two senior strikers would always be risky for the first half of the season; leaving him with one for a time is unforgivable.

There have been commendable aspects to his dealings - namely the swoop to bring Rafael van der Vaart to the club and the low cost approach to building a top four capable squad, all the while planning a multi-million pound stadium and regeneration of the area. But he also failed to secure Joao Moutinho, Villas-Boas' number one target - a player they are pursuing once again - and an intelligent target man capable of leading the line as a 'one'. 

Reports of an official bid for Internacional's striker Leandro Damiao offer encouragement, but for a saga that has dragged on for almost three years, no-one will be anticipating a swift conclusion to this move - particularly after the player distanced himself from a January switch. 

Though the wheels have been set in motion commendably early, the Brazilian club are notoriously tricky to deal with as well, despite being a club partner. No-one expects this to be tied up in January.

So it leaves Tottenham with one striker, and an out of form striker at that. Yet, the problem is not with Defoe, it lies somewhere between the club and Adebayor. 

For his part in this mess, it was always possible that he would change his mind and represent Togo at a major tournament. 

The club, therefore, can only blame themselves for not devising a contingency plan for a situation they should have seen coming well in advance. Spurs will have to hope they get by without him.

Follow Jay Jaffa on ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/1717/editorial/2013/01/10/3661384/adebayor-mess-leaves-tottenham-feeling</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Juventus emerged the victors after 120 minutes of hard-fought football in front of their own fans, as they squeezed past AC Milan 2-1 in Wednesday's Coppa Italia quarter-final. 
 Don't Miss EXCL: Juve eye Muriel-Boakye swapEXCL: Juve join Milan in race for MugniDrogba's agent confirms Juve contactRobinho out of Milan side to face Juve Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Parma pound; 52.50 Draw pound; 36.00 Juventus pound; 16.70 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Parma pound; 50.00 Draw pound; 35.00 Juventus pound; 17.27 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Parma pound; 50.00 Draw pound; 35.00 Juventus pound; 17.30 
The Bianconeri fell behind to Stephan El Shaarawy's early strike, but levelled through Sebastian Giovinco before Mirko Vucinic sent the game in extra time. 

The crowd at Juventus Stadium was treated to a frenetic start to the quarter-final clash, as both teams pushed forward in search of an early opener. Massimo Ambrosini was the first man to take aim at goal, his early snapshot pushed over the bar by Marco Storari with barely two minutes on the clock. It was a warning for Juve, and one the home team failed to heed as they fell almost instantly behind. 

Kevin-Prince Boateng stretched the home defence with a storming run down the left flank, and did enough to turn in a low cross from the byeline. Giampaolo Pazzini was intelligent enough to let the ball run and it was El Shaarawy who took full advantage, as the Serie A top scorer curled a well-taken effort past the flailing Storari and into the corner of the net. 

Milan's attacking prowess could not hide certain deficiencies at the back, though, and Alessandro Matri had a golden chance to level proceedings after connecting with a cross from Sebastian Giovinco, but unmarked, the striker nodded wide. 

Fortunately for the hosts, that miss was a minor blip on their way to an equaliser. Francesco Acerbi was the villain for Milan, after giving away possession he compounded his error by felling Matri on the edge of the area. A marvellous free-kick from Giovinco gave Marco Amelia no chance, and with just 12 minutes played Juve were back on level terms at 1-1. 

The Rossoneri continued to press in search of the lead, but in truth were rather lucky to enter half-time level both on the scoresheet and in terms of personnel. Giovinco was handed another chance to strike from a dead-ball situation, but this time Amelia was equal to it and pulled off a spectacular save to tip the effort over. The youngster then failed to capitalise on Acerbi's scuffed header that put him clean through against Amelia, firing wide on his left foot.

Phillippe Mexes, meanwhile, pushed his luck by obstructing Storari, having already earned a booking for a vicious challenge, but to Juve's disappointment he was given a final warning.

The game continued in the same open, high-octane fashion after the interval, and Giovinco again had the chance to put his side in the ascendancy. The striker attempted to take advantage of a fortuitous deflection from close range, but he failed to make decent contact and Amelia had little problem in saving down low. At the other end Boateng also troubled the keeper, forcing Storari to get down and stop a decent effort from distance.

As extra-time loomed both teams appeared to lower their tempo, playing more cautiously in anticipation of either an additional 30 minutes, or a decisive strike coming on the counter. Teenage Milan substitute M'Baye Niang briefly raised pulses with a jinking run that was finally ended on the edge of the area by Leonardo Bonucci. In the dying minutes Niang again went close as his header flew wide of the post, but at the final whistle the game remained deadlocked at 1-1. 

The match had barely kicked off for the 30 minutes of added time before Juve forced themselves into the lead for the first time. Emanuele Giaccherini did well with a tireless run to spearhead the break, and his deep pass rebounded into the path of Mirko Vucinic, who made no mistake in finishing from close range. 

Massimiliano Allegri's side desperately threw themselves forward in search of a way back into the match, but were frustrated in their onslaught by a determined backline and the heroic Storari, as they bid farewell to the Coppa Italia.

The victory books Antonio Conte's team into the semi-finals; where they join Lazio, who entered the last-four thanks to a comprehensive 3-0 victory over Catania. ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/1036/coppa-italia/2013/01/09/3660541/juventus-2-1-ac-milan-aet-vucinic-t</link>
 </news>
 <news>
 <content><![CDATA[ Gennaro Gattuso believes Vincenzo Montella has the credentials to one day replace Massimiliano Allegri in the AC Milan hotseat.
 Don't Miss Gattuso: Italy is not a racist countryGattuso: I almost left AC Milan for BayernGattuso reveals interest in coachingGattuso: I left Milan because of Allegri Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Sampdoria pound; 37.50 Draw pound; 33.00 Milan pound; 20.00 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Sampdoria pound; 36.00 Draw pound; 33.00 Milan pound; 20.50 Bet: pound;5 pound;10 pound;20 pound;50 pound;100 Returns: Sampdoria pound; 37.50 Draw pound; 32.50 Milan pound; 20.50 
The 35-year-old, who won Serie A and the Champions League twice with AC Milan, claims the former striker has demonstrated great potential in his embryonic coaching career and tipped him to make the move to San Siro.

"He represents a fresh face and a new mentality, and his sides play good football," Gattuso told Sky Sports 24.

Montella made his name spearheading Roma's attack for a decade, with the capital club appointing him caretaker coach for a short spell in 2011.

The 38-year-old, known for his aeroplane goal celebration, took the reigns at Catania for the 2011-2012 season before being handed the Fiorentina job last summer.

The former Fulham and Sampdoria striker has steered his new club to an impressive fourth place in Serie A after 19 matches, three places better off than AC Milan.


 ]]></content>
 <link>http://www.goal.com/en/news/10/italy/2013/01/09/3660664/gattuso-tips-montella-as-future-ac-milan-coa</link>
 </news>
</root>
